Today is the day of the semifinal game.
Except for Ji Hoo and me,
no one got eliminated
and made it back into the competition.
We were the only two people
who experienced the Revival Match.
Our determination is on another level.
I'm ready to draw
my Crescent Moon Blade...
and wield it against these people
like Guan Yu.
Today's weather is amazing.
Before I knew it,
I made it to the semifinal match.
There are eight of us now.
A large group of players made it
to the semifinal match.
I wanted my team to take the lead...
and earn the right to advance
to the final match.
I've been aiming for that in my head.
I made it this far thanks to my team.
I made it back into the game
by showing everyone what I was made of...
during the do-or-die Deathmatch.
I wanted to play the semifinal match
on my own.
That's what I had in mind before the game.
So this is the semifinal match.
Will we be playing...
individually?
Probably.
No more headaches then.
Headaches?
We'll be at a disadvantage
if it's a team match.
- Why?
- Seong Beom and Jin Ho will team up.
It'd be nice if they split up.
- Seong Beom and Jin Ho?
- Yes.
That's a dangerous duo.
Seong Beom and Jin Ho.
If I can,
I'd love to see them get eliminated.
The players I see
as big threats would be...
Naturally, they're Jin Ho and Seong Beom.
I also have my eyes on Seung Yong.
The weather is great today.
Even if I have to...
be attacked by the majority again
like yesterday,
I'll fight to the very end.
Seung Yong helped me a lot yesterday.
So I want to do my best,
so both of us can survive today.
"I need to be on my toes starting today."
"This is the moment
I've been playing for."
That crossed my mind.
Please gather in the main hall.
My gosh.
- Race? Is it a race or what?
- My gosh.
- What race?
- L and R?
- What's this?
- Gosh.
(Surprised)
They stand for left and right.
- I see cars. This is a race.
- How interesting.
- What?
- This looks fun.
The car race looks fun.
I wonder what kind of game
we're going to play.
It looks like
it's going to be a race or something.
There are eight of us.
And say that it's a race.
In the end, it's going to be a game
of passing, chasing, and blocking.
That's what I'm expecting.
That made me think that
I might need to form an alliance.
I didn't know what it was,
but it looked like a race.
It seemed I was the only one
without a driver's license.
I thought that might be a disadvantage.
I was hoping it would be a game
where we had to play individually...
or a game where the Minority Alliance
would have a shot...
at beating the Majority Alliance.
Hello.
I'd like to welcome the eight of you...
to the semifinal match of Bloody Game X.
I will now explain the rules
of the semifinal match.
The semifinal match is the last hurdle
before the final match.
It will be an eight-player
individual competition.
As for the number of players
advancing to the final match,
it's a total of four players.
For the final match of Bloody Game X,
there will be three tournament rounds.
Round One of the final match...
will be between 1st and 4th place
of the semifinal match.
Round Two of the final match...
will be between 2nd and 3rd place
of the semifinal match.
The top two players
of the semifinal match...
will earn the right to choose the game
for their final match respectively.
The winners of each round...
will advance to Round Three.
Then the final winner of Bloody Game X
will be decided.
The game for the semifinal match
will be revealed now.
is called...
(Prediction Race)
Prediction Race.
Prediction Race will be
an eight-player individual competition.
In this game,
players must move their race car...
through placing bets and arranging cards.
Each player is given a race car...
of a distinct color...
and a gear board
featuring left and right slots.
Before the game, players will make...
a secret prediction of their final ranking
in the race.
Once predictions are locked in,
all players will receive 5 betting cards
from 1 to 5.
When a player uses up all five cards
in their hand,
they will immediately receive
a new set of five cards.
During a round,
actions are taken in order.
Betting, playing movement cards,
and moving race cars.
This is the betting phase.
Movement cards come in a set of 12.
Three random movement cards...
will be revealed in Areas A, B, C, and D.
Players must make a secret bet...
in the Voting Room
with one of their betting cards...
on 1 of the 4 areas.
The player with the highest bid
in each area...
will claim...
three movement cards from that area.
In the event of a tie for the highest bid,
the player with the second-highest bid
will claim the cards.
(Won)
The next stage is
playing the movement cards.
The successful bidders will go in order...
to place the movement cards
either on their gear board...
or other players' gear board.
The players also have an option
to discard the cards...
if they wish.
Once the successful bidders
finish playing their movement cards,
the race cars will be moved.
Once both slots of the gear board
are filled,
the race car will be moved
based on these following rules.
One. If the numbers on both sides
of the gear board match,
the race car moves straight
by that number of spaces.
Two. If the numbers don't match,
the race car moves straight
by the lower number,
followed by a diagonal move equal
to the difference of the two numbers...
toward the direction of the bigger number.
Three. If there are a reverse card
and a number card on the gear board,
the race car moves backward
by the number shown on the card.
If both slots contain reverse cards...
or if a reverse card is paired with zero,
the race car cannot move,
and the cards will be discarded.
The race cars move in order,
beginning with the first player
for that round.
If only one slot of the gear board
is filled,
the player can keep the card
for the next round.
Here are the variables...
when moving the race cars.
One. When a race car bumps into the wall,
it overturns.
The player can neither move the race car
nor put down cards on the gear board...
in the next round.
Two. If a race car collides
with another race car,
it goes on top of the car.
The car underneath cannot move.
Three. If there's another race car
in front of a player's race car...
at the starting line,
the booster activated by the slipstream
allows the race car...
to start two spaces farther ahead.
The game can last up to 20 rounds.
If a race car crosses the finish line,
the game ends at the end of that round.
As for the final rankings,
players with correct predictions...
win top positions,
ordered by their race results.
Next,
players with incorrect predictions...
are determined by their race results.
(Players with incorrect predictions)
There's a hidden rule
in the semifinal match.
It will be revealed to all players
before Round Six...
begins.
Prediction Race will begin shortly.
All players must submit...
their predicted ranking
in the Voting Room.
Winning first place
isn't the goal of this game.
Finishing the race in the predicted rank
is the most important.
But if I reveal my predicted rank,
other players might try to get in my way.
I can never let them
find out my prediction.
I have to hide my intention.
Then I must finish in the position
I want at the end...
to win the game.
The key point of this game is that
I must conceal my prediction...
while trying to figure out
other players' predictions.
I think the Majority Alliance
would have an upper hand in this game.
So I'll have to take that approach
no matter what.
There's an advantageous approach
to win the game.
So why wouldn't I take it?
Actually, I like turn-based games.
A psychological element comes
into play in this game.
We don't know each other's predictions.
Will they go hard from the start?
Or will they take their time at first?
This kind of decision could mislead them.
Well, since it's the type of game I like,
I want to do well
and earn a chance to advance...
to the final match.
You will have ten minutes...
to strategize before the game begins.
Do we need an alliance for this game?
Well, the thing is,
if my car ends up getting overturned,
I can't help anyone at that point.
By the nature of the game,
it's impossible to win
if you play this game on your own.
I thought forming an alliance was a must.
Let's say we play as a team.
Then it's better if our turns are...
back-to-back.
If our turns aren't consecutive,
other people might play their cards
and get in our way.
How much money do you have?
I have... I see.
I might have the most amount.
Right. You do...
- because...
- Seong Beom.
Why don't we play individually this time?
- Oh, that's...
- You don't want to?
- I'm not sure.
- You're not sure?
The silver lining was that
only four of us could advance.
Forming a five-player alliance
would be pointless.
If the Majority Alliance
wins all the cards...
and dictates the flow of play,
there isn't much
the Minority Alliance can do.
This time around,
I'll keep my head in the game...
and do my best to stop them...
from forming the Majority Alliance.
What do you think about
strongly advocating independent play?
But I don't know if they'll listen to me
and play individually.
I doubt playing as a group
will be a catch-all solution.
But this game is
all about gathering information.
That's true.
What do you think? Should we team up?
Would it be better if we were
to make predictions as a group?
In my opinion, it might be better
to share our predictions...
and help each other with the cards...
when we place bets.
- Yes.
- What did you say?
Right.
So you mean we should play together.
And let's not forget that
you have the most funds right now.
- So you can decide the order.
- Yes.
Since I had the largest amount
of personal funds,
I was able to determine
the order of players.
With that in my favor, working
with other players from time to time...
will be very important.
It looks like
those guys don't want to team up.
- What? They want to play individually?
- Yes.
We can at least talk to them.
Well, we'd like to talk to everyone.
Are you planning to form an alliance
for this game?
Or are you planning to play individually?
It depends on the situation.
We could be giving help or receiving it.
You could share your predictions,
so you could help or receive help
from each other.
To be honest,
that's the best-case scenario for me.
Making predictions
without discussing them...
would be best, right?
- Because that will be a fair game?
- He has a point.
- Sung Joo, let's go out for a smoke.
- Sure.
I'd pick playing without an alliance...
if I have to vote.
Of course, I don't want to get eliminated.
I don't want
to ride anyone's coattails anymore.
I really don't want to do that.
People are complex creatures.
I had to keep relying on these nobodies.
When I had to do that,
I got a reality check.
I came here, determined to survive
even if I had to be a cockroach.
Since that's not who I am,
I'd hit the breaking point.
The mental breaking point.
Honestly,
looking at the current situation...
and the remaining players,
if I were to team up with Jin Ho
and Seong Beom, I wouldn't get eliminated.
But I really don't want to cave
into their alliance and join them.
I don't want any ambiguity.
- If we're going to play individually,
- We should do it properly?
we should gather everyone
and be in agreement before we begin.
Or if you want to play as a team,
we should tell everyone about that.
So other players can keep that in mind.
If you say you'll play individually,
but it turns out
the two of you were playing together,
- that's annoying and pathetic.
- Right.
Let's say we don't form an alliance.
But it looks like I might end up...
- working with players I don't want.
- Right.
Here's the only way
we can play as an alliance.
The four of us...
can discuss strategies
and share our predictions. That's one way.
- It might not work with four people.
- Two people?
- Everything?
- Yes.
But here's something to think about.
Looking back, we won Money Challenges...
and helped our teammates survive.
Is there a reason
why we shouldn't work as a team for this?
- You have a point too.
- Yes.
They're pushing for individual play...
in an important game like this...
because they know an alliance
would put them at a disadvantage.
I'm not so happy to hear that.
He's just so annoying.
As for Seong Beom,
he always thinks he's the star.
If I wanted to team up with anyone,
it would be Jin Ho.
I don't have any interest
in teaming up with Seong Beom.
Let's talk about this quickly.
I think it's okay to team up
after placing bets.
But we shouldn't team up before that.
I think that's fair.
But why is that fair?
At the end of the day,
this survival game is played by people.
I made my moves strategically,
always considering
who to keep by my side...
and who to face as my opponents
the whole time.
I really did my best
during Money Challenges.
So my teammates didn't get eliminated.
If you say that doesn't matter now
and we should play individually,
you're only arguing that
because that gives you an advantage.
That's not being fair.
He had a valid point.
But he didn't have to be so rude
when he spoke.
Despite that,
I still appealed to their emotional side.
I think I was successful in setting
the tone that a Majority Alliance...
would be bad for the game.
His speech was artificial too.
You can let things go, Seong Beom.
We all know that you're the man.
Both of you have a point.
I think playing individually
for the entire game won't be possible.
If anyone wants to form an alliance,
they should announce it to everyone.
Secondly, even if there are alliances,
it won't be
the majority versus the minority.
There can be a cap
on the number of players like 2 or 3.
Once we set a cap on that,
their options will be limited.
Forming an alliance might not make
a huge difference.
We brought it up
because playing individually...
would be more comfortable for people
without an alliance.
In the end, we all need
some form of alliance to play this game.
Once that became the nature of our game,
we have no choice...
but to lean toward forming alliances.
And that's why people do form alliances.
Not to repeat what happened yesterday,
I'm proposing that
we come up with a minimal set of rules.
That's completely doable,
and that's what I'm suggesting.
I think two people would be enough.
I'd prefer to play individually.
I know we won yesterday.
But I got the feeling that...
the alliance was much bigger
than the game needed.
- But...
- I want it to be a small alliance.
during Blind Auction,
Teams P1, R, and C made an alliance.
I'm not saying that what we did was fair.
- How did you feel then?
- What?
- How did you feel after that game?
- Even though we won,
- it was like yesterday.
- It didn't feel good?
- Right. It was the same.
- Once we play, we should go all the way.
They always have excuses.
They wanted to play individually
because they were at a disadvantage.
But they left that out.
"You guys are so awful
for playing as the majority."
"You're such cowards."
Saying things like that...
makes them bigger cowards.
He made it sound like
not making an alliance...
would leave me at a loss.
Of course,
if we only considered winning and losing,
his argument sounded reasonable.
But I'm sick of this dynamic.
I don't envy them.
There's going to be a bloodbath.
This is Bloody Game now.
For this game, having a lot of people
on your team won't necessarily...
give you an advantage.
At max,
it will be a three-player alliance.
If so, it's best to play with my team
since I've been playing with them...
the whole season.
It looks like Seong Beom, Hye Seon,
- and I will form an alliance.
- Yes.
It could be a 3-3-2 split.
Or it could be a 3-2-2-1 split.
You guys can discuss that
and decide what you want to do.
- Yes. Sounds good.
- Should we do that?
- Yes. It doesn't matter.
- All right.
That should be all right.
Why? I'll play on my own.
Playing solo? That's cool.
I'll play on my own.
If we have to pick our team,
isn't it better that we team up?
Or we could invite Keun Woo
and make it a three-player team.
Given the history, Ji Hoo will team up...
with Seung Yong. Right?
Let's say we play together. Keun Woo...
Having three people on the team
could be tough.
Keun Woo, do you want to play with us?
- What?
- How about the three of us?
My gosh. What's the point? I'll just play.
Join us. Let's play together.
Or it could be a 3-2-1-1-1 split.
Yes. That's pretty cool.
If we do that,
they won't know our dynamic.
- Right.
- It might confuse them.
- It could be like we're going solo.
- Yes.
- I want to be on my own today.
- Okay.
- On your own?
- Yes.
I want to play the first round
on my own too.
Do you want to play individually?
Their alliance won't put us
at a disadvantage.
- Not necessarily.
- Right.
No one can figure out our predictions
or our dynamic.
- Yes. Sure.
- I want to play on my own.
I made it this far
by relying on other people.
I just want to play on my own
before I leave the show.
- I'll stop piggybacking on other people.
- Exactly.
I think I have an upper hand here.
As for Sung Joo, I can persuade him...
to join me whenever I want.
As I expected, Team P3...
formed an alliance all on their own.
By doing so,
they have shut down any possibilities
to other alliances...
even before the game.
Here's what we discussed.
We don't want to form an alliance out
in the open from the get-go.
They're openly working together.
In my opinion,
it might actually backfire...
because they can easily become targets.
- I see.
- Okay.
If you want to go after anyone,
I think going after them makes more sense.
- We have to see the order of turns first.
- Right.
Hye Seon has the largest amount
of personal funds.
Come to the Voting Room and
decide the order of turns for the players.
They might struggle
to understand the game.
I put them first.
I see. I think
the order you have looks pretty good.
I think switching the 1st and 3rd players
could be better.
The 1st and 3rd players?
I wanted to separate the players
from other alliances...
while placing ourselves back-to-back.
Ta-da.
You have submitted the order.
- Please go back to the main hall.
- Thank you.
Here's the order of turns.
The red car with number one goes
to Jeong Keun Woo.
I'm first?
The sky blue car with number two goes
to Kang Ji Hoo.
The yellow car with number three goes
to YunB.
The green car with number four goes
to Heo Seong Beom.
The blue car with number five goes
to Hong Jin Ho.
The purple car with number six goes
to Choi Hye Seon.
The white car with number seven goes
to Hyun Sung Joo.
The black car with number eight goes
to Shin Seung Yong.
(Jeong Keun Woo, Kang Ji Hoo, YunB,
Heo Seong Beom, Hong Jin Ho,)
(Choi Hye Seon, Hyun Sung Joo,
Shin Seung Yong)
(Jeong Keun Woo)
(The 1st player of Round 1)
You want to get rid of me first.
Is that it?
Right? You want me gone first.
I thought it would take some time...
to get the hang of it
for the first player.
He might be at a disadvantage
in Round One.
But there will be a point
when his position will come in handy...
as we keep playing.
I thought he might not maximize
the advantage as much as the others.
And Seong Beom is number four...
which means he could be
the first one to play in the last round.
That's why I put down...
Seong Beom, Jin Ho, and me
for numbers 4, 5, and 6.
Actually,
going second is the absolute worst.
The game will end in 20 rounds.
I'll go last in Round 19.
And I'll be the penultimate player
in Round 20.
She gave me that spot.
Then she kept me and Seung Yong as far
as possible, so we couldn't control...
the flow of the game.
I sensed
that this wouldn't be an easy one.
You will now predict your rank
in the race.
Enter the Voting Room in order.
How will you predict yours?
I think they'll predict
1st, 2nd, and 3rd place.
You think they'd be that foolish?
It's such a foolish thing to do.
One of them has to settle
for a lower place.
I see. So they might predict
1st, 2nd, and 8th place?
That's possible.
With three people on the team,
one of them should go
for a spot in the top three.
Another one for the middle ranks.
And the last one
for either 7th or 8th place.
They'd think whoever goes for the bottom
would get their prediction right for sure.
If I were playing individually,
I was going to pick 7th or 8th place.
There's a risk,
but getting the prediction right...
would increase the chances
of advancing to the final match.
But if we're playing as a team,
one of us should go for a spot
in the top three.
And the other one should go for a spot
in the middle three.
I think we should go for higher ranks.
Go for it. Pick either 2nd or 3rd place.
I'll take one in the low-middle tier.
- So second place?
- Go with that.
That might be a better strategy.
We need to come up with a strategy
with the best...
- The most-balanced strategy?
- Yes, the most-balanced strategy.
If we all correctly predict our ranks,
- the one with a higher rank wins.
- Yes.
But if we fail to predict our ranks,
the one with a higher rank
in the race wins.
Getting our prediction right
is the most important.
But that might be difficult.
Only four of us can advance.
Let's say
all of us correctly predict our ranks.
Only the top four players can advance.
The race rankings...
We don't have to go for 6th or 7th place.
I think we'll be safe
up to 4th and 5th place.
Most importantly,
our predictions can't overlap.
Right.
I want to drive my race car...
in style right to the very end.
- You can drive it or sabotage it.
- Yes.
- It might even overturn.
- Exactly.
- You could get in someone's way.
- Sure.
I'm a man with a driver's license.
Is it helpful for you if we speed up...
the race?
- She's feeling you out.
- I'll start with a bang.
- That will be better for you?
- Yes. I'm going first.
When players fail
to predict their rank correctly,
top finishers in the race will advance.
I had a feeling that a lot of players...
probably chose a spot in the top three.
Keun Woo, please head to the Voting Room.
Keun Woo,
choose your predicted rank in the race.
I was playing on my own.
I thought about ways to win the game
while going solo.
Keun Woo,
you predicted you would be in sixth place.
I shouldn't try to beat the alliance.
I'll be a little behind the middle group.
I decided to take things slow
when the game began.
So I predicted I'd be in sixth place.
Ji Hoo, you predicted
you would be in second place.
My strategy is simple.
I'll pretend
I really want to win first place.
I'll try to pull ahead
right out of the gate.
When I do that,
they'll try to pull me back.
I'll pretend that they got their way.
But at the end...
"I really wanted to win 1st place,
but I'm in 2nd place."
"But actually, I wanted second place."
Tricking them is my strategy.
YunB, choose your predicted rank.
The best-case scenario is...
finishing the race
in the rank I predicted.
I sort of got the big picture.
Seong Beom, choose your predicted rank.
I have a good feeling about this.
Jin Ho,
choose your predicted rank.
(Hong Jin Ho completes his prediction.)
Okay.
Hye Seon, choose your predicted rank.
Sung Joo,
choose your predicted rank.
Seung Yong, choose your predicted rank.
(Seung Yong completes his prediction too.)
Predictions for the race rankings
have ended.
(Predictions have ended.)
I can see it in your eyes
that you picked third place.
I can't keep a poker face.
Don't say stuff like that.
It looks like you put down third place.
Did you bet on coming in last?
First place or last place?
Will you end the race early
or after Round 20?
You three must be on the same boat, right?
Round One will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Keun Woo)
Place 1 of your colored cards
numbered 1 through 5...
in one of the areas from A to D where
your target movement card is located.
The player with...
the highest number in each area
claims the cards.
If two or more players put down
the same number,
the player with the next-highest number
claims the cards.
I think we can try for C.
But I'm going to put down a one
in this round.
You can put down a five for C.
We thought about
getting Hye Seon's car to move forward.
To make that happen,
winning Area C would give her an edge.
But other people might also bet a five.
Should I put down a four for C?
That's iffy. Hear me out.
Betting a 4 makes sense
if someone else bets a 5 simultaneously.
- That's the only possibility you'd win.
- I see.
Or 1 of us can help you win with a 4.
- But...
- That's unnecessary.
I'm not sure if it's the right move
considering the opportunity cost.
- I agree. That doesn't sound right.
- Okay.
In anticipation of tied numbers
in one area,
if other players from the alliance play
low numbers together,
it boosts the alliance's chances
of securing the cards.
Is it necessary to burn our cards
in the beginning?
Taking an early lead won't be good
in my opinion...
because there's a booster.
It's better to be trailing behind
up until the second half.
In Round One,
I'm letting other players take a lead,
so I can stay back
and try to read other players' strategies.
There's no point
in winning the target cards.
Jin Ho. You've placed Card One in Area C.
I decided to discard low numbers
in Round One.
- Card One to Area B.
- Seong Beom.
You've placed Card One in Area B.
I wasn't trying to win anything,
so I put down a one.
These are mine.
Hello.
Sung Joo.
Place your card
in the area of your choice.
I wanted to show them...
my car moving forward aggressively
with the cards I won.
I'll put it down in Area C.
Sung Joo.
You've placed Card Five in Area C.
(Area C already has 2 5s.)
The best-case scenario is that...
we win Area C and move forward.
Yes.
I'll put down a five in Area C.
Okay.
Then why don't you put down a one there?
I think it's a good idea
that you come into Area C.
We might get a tie with five.
Putting down a one there...
doesn't sound efficient
even if we anticipate that.
So you want to play for the area
no one will go for, right?
Area D doesn't look that popular.
I'm still thinking.
Ji Hoo.
You've placed Card Five in Area C.
- I'll go here.
- Seung Yong.
You've placed Card One in Area A.
What's that called?
There are two slots on the gear board.
So that gives us only 16 available slots
for the cards, right?
- Right.
- Okay.
But you don't have to put down any cards.
- Is that allowed?
- Yes, it's allowed.
We have three minutes
to put down our cards.
During those three minutes,
we don't have to put down any cards.
Keun Woo, how is it
that you understood the rules so well?
You know what?
He's a master of survival shows.
- The cards get discarded.
- Yes.
Because I was on my own,
I was able to understand the rules
super quickly.
I had no one else to rely on.
Even before the game began,
I had already understood
all of the game rules.
What if two players put down...
the same number?
- That area disappears then?
- It's a bust then.
- It's a bust?
- No one can claim the cards.
It's a bust then.
Ask me about the rules, Hye Seon.
I know every rule.
- Right.
- Yes.
(Jeong Keun Woo...)
(and YunB place their bet.)
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
Announce them now.
Area A...
- goes to Seung Yong.
- Yes.
How big of a number did you put down?
(Seung Yong claims the cards with a 1.)
- Darn it.
- Area B goes to Seong Beom.
(Seong Beom also claims the cards
with a 1.)
Area C goes...
That's mine.
to YunB.
Area D goes to Keun Woo.
We're all starting from zero.
Who would pick a reverse card?
If I win the cards, then I win.
If I don't, then I don't.
I put down my lowest value card
to test the waters.
And I won.
- Area C must've been a bust.
- Wait.
- Right, it was a bust.
- I didn't win either.
I put down a one there
in case it was a bust.
(Jin Ho put down a 1 in Area C
in case Hye Seon's card was wasted.)
She put down a five.
We had a feeling
the others would put down a five too.
As a contingency plan,
I decided to put down a 1 or a 2...
in case 2 or more players put down a 5,
so we could win the cards.
- YunB must've put down 2, 3, or 4.
- Yes.
(The competition was intense
to become the winner of Area C.)
I won the cards.
You've placed Card Four in Area C.
I was certain that
someone would put down a five in Area C.
So I put down a four as insurance.
(Distributing the movement cards)
Okay. Thank you.
You will now place your movement cards.
Keun Woo, please place your cards.
- Where will you place them?
- What?
- I have a reverse card.
(Keun Woo places the movement cards
on Seung Yong's board,)
(so he can move forward.)
Holy moly.
Good for you, Seung Yong.
Vroom.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
He made it back
from the Deathmatch yesterday.
I'm testing the waters.
My guess is almost everyone probably...
wanted to place at the top.
"Okay. Go for it."
I was testing the waters
by helping him move forward.
You now have one minute left.
(He places the reverse card
on YunB's gear board.)
Gosh, it's impossible to guess his moves.
It's impossible to guess his moves.
My goodness.
Keun Woo hates me.
I really like Keun Woo.
But I think he hates me...
if I'm being honest with you.
I don't know when it started.
But it might have started
when I wanted to get rid of Ji Min.
YunB, please place your cards.
(He won the movement cards,
but he can't move forward now.)
You can't move forward anyway, right?
What happens if I have a reverse card...
and a two?
We're at the starting line.
You can't move...
- backward.
- Exactly.
I don't think
you can move forward in this round.
- He can't.
- Right.
- I can't do anything, right?
So you can help me instead.
- You're a go-getter.
- Yes.
Placing a number card on the right slot
doesn't do anything for me, right?
Right.
- I need to finish near the top.
- What?
- Okay.
If you don't have any use for them,
could you help me this time?
You need to finish near the top.
Should we share our prediction
and keep it between us?
- I'll tell you mine.
- Okay.
I need to finish second.
That's a relief. I need to finish third.
- Okay.
- Right.
(YunB predicted he'd be in 3rd place.)
I chose third place for a simple reason.
I don't have to be aggressive
in the beginning of the game.
With third place, I have more options
to trick other players.
Ji Hoo's prediction was second place.
Given our predictions,
forming an alliance works in our favor.
Second and third place.
We might be able
to win 2nd and 3rd place...
toward the end.
YunB, you now have one minute left.
(Placing a 4 on Ji Hoo's gear board)
He's helping Ji Hoo move forward.
He's going straight ahead.
Ji Hoo is in the lead.
- Give me one too.
- YunB,
your time is up.
Your cards will be discarded.
(The rest of the cards are discarded.)
What a waste.
Watching the cards get discarded...
felt like such a waste.
YunB must want to finish
between 5th and 7th place.
It must be somewhere around there.
Seong Beom, please place your cards.
I'll move forward first.
Yes. You can do that.
Jin Ho. Hye Seon. Does anyone want a card?
Me. Help me move forward.
(He places a 2 and a 3 on his gear board.)
(He places a 1 on Hye Seon's gear board.)
Seung Yong, please place your cards.
- Do you want to move forward?
- Yes.
- What should I do?
- Help me start the engine.
What do you want? What should I do?
Put down a three on my board.
Then play safe with the rest.
All right.
Ji Hoo must be in a hurry.
Help him move forward.
They're working together.
Of course, he has to do that.
(Placing a 3 on Ji Hoo's gear board)
Go ahead.
(Placing a 1 on Hye Seon's gear board)
Don't move.
Moving back zero spaces.
All the movement cards have been placed.
(Ji Hoo, Seong Beom, Hye Seon,
and Seung Yong can move their car.)
Ji Hoo, please pick your starting space.
I'll start here.
Ji Hoo, you chose Lane Six.
Three spaces forward...
and one space left.
Look at you, pulling ahead.
That's so cool.
YunB, you cannot move.
Seong Beom,
please pick your starting space.
I'll choose Lane Four.
Seong Beom, you chose Lane Four.
(Seong Beom chooses to start from Lane 4.)
Two spaces forward...
and one space right.
(Seong Beom)
My booster could get activated.
(As he's right behind Ji Hoo,
his booster may be activated in Round 2.)
Ji Hoo is going before you.
He'll try to get away.
- If he can't move, you'll get it.
- Right.
Hye Seon, please pick your starting space.
I'll choose...
- Which one?
- Lane Four.
One space forward.
Seung Yong,
please pick your starting space.
I'll go with Lane Six.
One space forward and one space left.
(Seung Yong)
I just helped you get out on the road.
Thank you.
I guess I can expect a similar pattern.
- Right.
- Yes.
All players have completed their moves.
Getting the car to move
is harder than I thought.
Please don't make it difficult for me,
Keun Woo.
I made it difficult for you?
You gave me a reverse card.
I see. You have to finish near the top?
- I...
- Do you need to go forward quickly?
That's better for me.
I don't even know
who gave what card in Round One.
What if YunB predicted he'd finish eighth?
Look at him. He's acting again.
Round Two will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Ji Hoo)
After looking at the numbers,
I went in as fast as possible.
I put down a four...
to win 2, 1, and 3 in Round 2.
With 2, 1, and 3,
people will think
that they'd be able to pull ahead.
If I go for these numbers,
they might think I went for a high rank.
I wanted to confuse them a little.
- How do you decide so fast?
- What?
When someone decides quickly,
the other players will feel
a sense of urgency.
Going into the Voting Room fast
was one of my strategies.
- Do you have to move forward?
- What?
You haven't left yet, right?
(His white race car hasn't crossed
the starting line yet.)
It's not up to me, you know?
You can make it happen this time.
I have to win to do that.
Let me know if you need help.
I'm going to play on my own for this game.
There might come a time
when you need help.
You can't be on your own
from start to finish.
I want to see how it pans out.
During the first half of the game,
I thought behaving in a way...
that they couldn't guess my prediction...
was the most important.
It didn't matter
if I won the cards or not.
That wasn't important in the first half.
They'll give me a new set of cards
once I run out.
Should I just put down a four in Area B?
- To play offense?
- Yes.
- That sounds good too.
(Area B has a reverse card.)
A lot of them moved ahead.
Which area will you go for?
If I want to win the cards,
I should pick an area with better odds.
I'll put down a three
considering the possibility...
that it might be a bust.
In the previous round,
we put down a five...
and a one.
But other players put down the same card.
I thought
that might not be a good strategy.
And I also thought
that we should split up for this round.
(Hye Seon bets a 4 on Area B.)
I'll do this.
(Seong Beom bets a 3 on Area C.)
Seong Beom.
You've placed Card Three in Area C.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
Are you going to bet low this round?
I think I need to bet high this round
and get a head start...
because after this round,
I'm late in the turn order.
It doesn't matter if I win good cards.
If they place bad cards on my gear board
to hold me back,
I won't be able to use
any of my good cards.
If I win the cards
and am the first one to place the cards,
I can place them wherever I want.
If I'm late in the turn order,
winning the cards doesn't matter.
My gear board could be full by my turn.
So I wouldn't be able to place
any of my cards.
When I'm going first,
I have to bet high
in order to win the cards no matter what.
When I'm late in the turn order,
I have to bet low...
and get rid of the low value cards.
So...
there was a set of cards with 3 and 4.
This set of cards was the best
for pushing ahead.
I was determined to win these cards.
I was the first one to place cards.
So I wanted to move forward
by placing them on my board.
- What did you and YunB talk about?
- What?
What did you and YunB talk about?
He needs to finish third.
So we promised to help each other.
I revealed mine,
but I didn't reveal yours.
Ji Hoo.
Come here.
So you and I know...
each other's rank.
Can you intervene,
so Seung Yong doesn't see me...
as his competition?
- Could you relay the message?
- Sure.
You go.
(Ji Hoo is passing messages
between YunB and Seung Yong.)
YunB wanted me to tell you that...
he didn't want you to see him
as competition.
Just tell him
that he and I won't have to...
- compete.
- Okay.
Seung Yong doesn't need to compete
against you.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
So our ranks must not overlap.
That's a relief.
I take it
his predicted rank isn't that high?
For now, Seung Yong...
is still on the fence
about bringing YunB...
into our alliance.
So, I shared my information...
while keeping Seung Yong's info safe.
I kept going back and forth
between them...
to discuss strategy.
It's bad if we go to the same one,
so I'll tell you.
I'm going to bet a four on C.
C?
Ji Hoo, you've bet on Area C...
(The three split up and bet.)
YunB, you've bet on Area A...
Seung Yong, you've placed Card Two
in Area D.
I want to go just one space this time.
If we don't go from the starting line,
doesn't that count as last place?
Probably.
But that's practically impossible.
- Right? It's 20 rounds.
- It's impossible.
Someone will put a card there.
Yes, they'll think
that someone bet on last place.
I will announce the betting results.
Area A goes to Keun Woo.
- He's taking all of them.
- Goodness.
You can't predict my moves.
It's so unpredictable.
Area B...
goes to Hye Seon.
Gosh, thank you.
Area C goes to Ji Hoo.
Area D goes to Jin Ho.
I got one.
Ji Hoo won big. I bet he'll go hard...
to get ahead.
I'm an auction expert.
I won two bids.
You're good at this.
Ji Hoo, please place your card.
I would like to go forward.
(Ji Hoo puts a 2 in YunB's gear board.)
(And he gives the rest to himself.)
- He's going fast.
- I'm so jealous.
I want to keep that car there.
- Which car?
- At the starting line.
- Whose car?
- Yours.
Son of a...
Come on, Keun Woo.
I thought we were friends.
- Which one is your car?
- That one.
- I should throw it away.
- If...
I get a reverse card,
I'm going to win it...
so I can keep sending him back.
Don't do that. You can be my superior.
Jin Ho, please place your card.
(Round 2, Ji Hoo, Jin Ho, Hye Seon,
Keun Woo)
(He places a 3 in his zone.)
Let me go forward.
Should I give one to Seong Beom?
Sure.
(He places a 1 in Seong Beom's area.)
I can put three in my area,
and Hye Seon can put two in mine.
- What?
- Seung Yong, you went forward.
You should keep going.
- Are you sure I can go?
- With zero.
(He gives Seung Yong a 0.)
- Keun Woo.
- Let me go forward.
Can you give it to me
if you're throwing it away?
- I'll make the decisions.
- Okay.
Don't tell me what to do with my cards.
Sorry.
Hye Seon, please place your cards.
Hye Seon, how are you going to attack?
It's all meaningless now.
(She planned on attacking Ji Hoo,
but his board is already full.)
You can give them to YunB.
Jin Ho, you should go.
(She gives a 2 to Jin Ho.)
- What about you, Hye Seon?
- You could send me off.
- Why isn't Ms. Choi going?
- What should I do?
Why don't we help each other out?
Ms. Choi...
With this?
(Round 2, Ji Hoo, Jin Ho, Hye Seon,
Keun Woo)
I didn't know how scary you were.
You're really...
I thought you wanted it.
(She gives a 1 to Seong Beom.)
(She gives the reverse card to YunB.)
- Sorry.
- Oh, no.
(Round 2, Ji Hoo, Jin Ho, Hye Seon,
Keun Woo)
Team P3's biggest mistake is...
still playing too closely together...
when it's an individual match now.
Like, "We're Team P3."
I hate it.
Keun Woo, please place your cards.
I don't care about anyone else now.
I'm going to go forward.
- You should.
- It's about time.
I went through a lot to win these.
Oh, my gosh.
Goodness.
- You're going so fast.
- Gosh.
Take one, Sung Joo.
(He gives a 2 to Sung Joo.)
He benefited just by sitting there.
Take one, Sung Joo.
I put one here.
Did you bet on placing eighth?
- He's keeping a poker face.
- You don't seem so happy.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, Seong Beom,
and Jin Ho can move.)
Ji Hoo, 3 spaces forward and 1 space left.
(Ji Hoo)
Oh, man.
This is going to end soon.
The game might end in Round Seven.
- Ji Hoo might finish it.
- Yes.
YunB, you cannot move.
(YunB's gear board is reset.)
Seong Beom, one space forward.
Vroom, vroom.
Jin Ho, please pick your starting space.
I'll go from Lane Three.
Two spaces forward and one space right.
Keun Woo, please pick your starting space.
(Keun Woo)
- I have 3 and 1, right?
- Yes, 3 and 1.
You could get on someone's back.
Exactly.
I had to start,
but I couldn't go before anybody else.
I'll take Lane Four.
I decided to collide.
Lane Four?
Yes.
Isn't that Hye Seon's?
He must have a plan.
Keun Woo, 1 space forward
and 2 spaces left.
Okay.
You've collided with Hye Seon's race car.
Oh, it happens instantly.
- Instantly.
- Yes.
- From the starting line?
- We don't jump over it.
- All players have completed their moves.
- Okay.
(Hye Seon's purple car is stuck
from the start.)
So heavy.
- Sorry.
- Is someone on your back?
It's so heavy.
It's a carpool.
Seriously.
- Keun Woo, did you bet on eighth place?
- What?
Did you bet on eighth place?
- Me? You can't figure it out, right?
- Yes.
Why aren't you going forward?
I realized that he either bet...
on 8th or 7th.
This is tough.
(Round 2 Movement Results)
(Player, predicted rank)
(Ji Hoo: 2nd, Keun Woo: 6th, YunB: 3rd)
Round Three will now begin.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(YunB)
If that team gets Area C, I'm doomed.
They can bring my car four spaces back.
(Ji Hoo)
So, I think it's best...
if you bet 5 and I bet 3.
Okay. That doesn't sound so bad.
I showed them
that I was trying to place first.
So, it was an important round...
where I had to win the reverse card
to protect myself.
Seung Yong, you've placed Card Five
in Area C.
Ji Hoo, you've placed Card Three...
in Area C. Is that correct?
Yes, it is.
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
Area A goes to YunB.
Area B goes to Jin Ho.
I won with that?
Area C...
goes to Ji Hoo.
Seong Beom, you've placed Card Five
in Area C.
Seung Yong bets five, the highest number,
and in case there are 2 players betting 5,
I also bet three.
It was a strategy to guarantee
that I win Area C.
(He's secured Area C
according to his plan.)
Area D has no winners.
No way.
No one bet on it?
(Round 3 Betting Results)
(Area A: YunB 5, Area B: Jin Ho 5,)
(Area C: Ji Hoo 3)
- You will now place your movement cards.
- Let's go.
YunB, please place your cards.
- Hye Seon's car is under Keun Woo's car.
- Yes.
Jin Ho is slightly ahead.
Maybe I should place a one
on Jin Ho's gear board.
Because he has fewer spaces
to go forward than Seong Beom.
- Because they're on one side?
- Yes.
- To hold Jin Ho in check.
- It makes sense.
(He places a 2 and a 3 in his slot.)
(He places a 1 in Jin Ho's slot.)
To me, it looked like
Jin Ho and Seong Beom...
were trying to go forward
as fast as possible.
We noticed that,
so we decided to disrupt their plan.
Jin Ho, please place your cards.
You're done already?
YunB is getting ahead.
(Jin Ho)
Oh, he blocked my right side.
(Round 3, YunB, Jin Ho, Ji Hoo)
I'll have to go forward.
And the other one...
(Jin Ho: 3, 0)
Ji Hoo, you should crash.
(Ji Hoo can't move to the right.)
(Not allowed)
(Ji Hoo: Reverse, 2, 4)
- Who should get three?
- Give me.
- What?
- Right.
- This one is too good.
- Give it to Seong Beom.
I will.
You're in the center,
so you're good to go, right?
- Yes.
- Take it.
(He places a 3 in Seong Beom's slot.)
Wasn't that a mistake?
- What?
- Wasn't that a mistake?
- Why?
- Oh, no.
- How is it a mistake?
- Why?
He made a mistake.
Because I have the reverse card.
- I see.
- I could...
I don't mind going back.
What if I had already calculated that?
You could be playing a mind game.
That's intense.
(Ji Hoo: Reverse, 2, 4)
Ji Hoo, please place your cards.
Let's see.
Give him the reverse card.
This is tricky.
Reverse him.
Okay.
I went through all that to go forward...
only to go back now.
(Ji Hoo: 2, 4)
Please give it to me!
(He places the rest of the cards.)
All the movement cards have been placed.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
(YunB, Seong Beom, Jin Ho,
and Seung Yong can move.)
The race cars will start moving now.
YunB, please pick your starting space.
- That's...
- I'll go from Lane Three.
- This is a tough one.
- YunB has chosen Lane Three.
He'll crash into Jin Ho.
YunB, 2 spaces forward and 1 space right.
What?
He's on top of you.
(He collides with Jin Ho.)
(YunB)
- YunB!
- You've collided with Jin Ho's race car.
Stop coming on to me.
Seong Beom, three spaces backward.
(Seong Beom)
You've collided
with Seung Yong's race car.
What happened?
It's a three-layer burger.
Jin Ho's race car cannot move.
Seung Yong's race car cannot move.
The three cars underneath
can't do anything.
I saw YunB behind me...
and thought he wouldn't attack me...
because I thought
he was still neutral at the time.
Then, YunB and Ji Hoo...
started whispering into each other's ears.
I thought it was strange,
and YunB instantly got on my back.
Although it's the early stage,
that move deeply hurt me.
(Round 3 Movement Results)
(Ji Hoo, YunB, Jin Ho, Seong Beom,
Seung Yong, Keun Woo, Hye Seon, Sung Joo)
Round Four will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Seong Beom)
(Keun Woo humming)
(He heads straight into the Voting Room.)
Keun Woo,
place your card
in the area of your choice.
Keun Woo, you've placed Card Three
in Area D.
- Is that correct?
- Yes.
I simply have to make my own choices,
plan by myself,
and make a move by myself.
But I'm also calculating things.
I'm not sure if I want to leave
Sung Joo's car alone.
(Sung Joo's race car hasn't departed yet.)
Did he really bet on eighth place?
He might have.
Sung Joo's car also...
didn't move an inch.
I realized he bet on 7th or 8th.
I ate too much breakfast. I had a salad.
What's your predicted rank?
- What?
- What's your predicted rank?
Did you bet on eighth?
You look too relaxed.
You know what? Forget it.
Sung Joo, you've placed Card Three
in Area B.
(He bets a 3 on Area B.)
(Round 4 Betting Results)
All players have placed their bets.
(Sung Joo 3, Seung Yong 3, Keun Woo 3)
I will announce the betting results.
Area A has no winners.
Area B goes to Sung Joo.
(Sung Joo wins Area B.)
Area C goes to Seung Yong.
Area D goes to Keun Woo.
- Keun Woo is good at bidding.
- Another one?
Three wins! I might have a shot.
He has to be a genius.
He's good.
I'll remain as an observer this time.
I can't believe I won that bid.
You will now place your movement cards.
Sung Joo, please place your cards.
(He places a 3 in his slot.)
Everyone, get on someone's back.
- We should.
- Get on.
(He places a 3 in Hye Seon's slot.)
Which one?
(He places a 2 in Keun Woo's slot.)
Thank you very much.
Seung Yong, please place your cards.
Move.
You got me out of the way.
(He places the remaining cards
in Seong Beom's and Ji Hoo's slots.)
Keun Woo, please place your cards.
Okay.
Let's find out.
(He places a 1 in his slot.)
I think I made a mistake.
I'll discard this one.
- He's so manly.
- So manly.
"Your precious card means nothing to me."
"You must be quick and firm
when you discard cards."
- I can't predict Keun Woo's next moves.
- All the movement cards have been placed.
He scares me.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
(Keun Woo, Seong Beom,
Hye Seon, and Sung Joo can move.)
The race cars will start moving.
(The race cars start moving.)
- Seong Beom, one space backward.
- Okay.
Hye Seon, you cannot move.
Okay.
Sung Joo, please pick your starting space.
Which one...
Seven!
Sung Joo, you've chosen Lane Seven.
I can't tell
if you're doing it on purpose.
- Right?
- He's...
- starting to confuse me.
- Two spaces forward and one space left.
(Sung Joo)
Keun Woo, one space forward...
and one space left.
Thanks.
Ji Hoo, you cannot move.
All players have completed their moves.
(Round 4 Movement Results)
(Ji Hoo, Keun Woo, YunB, Jin Ho, Sung Joo,
Seung Yong, Hye Seon, Seong Beom)
Round Five will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Jin Ho)
How should we use these cards?
We have to stop Ji Hoo,
get YunB away from us,
and move Seung Yong forward.
We have to do all three of these at once.
Who's going first?
I'm going first.
You'll place the cards first, right?
Yes, Hye Seon and I.
- Let's win Area B.
- Okay.
We put this card here.
(Seung Yong)
This one goes to Ji Hoo.
Give this one...
(Seung Yong, Ji Hoo)
to YunB.
Because we have to get this
out of the way.
(YunB, Jin Ho)
Tell Hye Seon to bet on Area C,
and you and I will bet on this.
I'll bet a three on Area C.
Okay.
Hye Seon, you've placed Card Three
in Area C.
- The second one.
- Jin Ho...
Seong Beom, you've placed Card Four
in Area B.
Place your card
in the area of your choice.
Please move to the main hall.
(Keun Woo and Sung Joo finish betting.)
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
Area A goes to Ji Hoo.
Nice.
Area B...
goes to Keun Woo.
Four wins in a row?
Keun Woo, you've placed Card Five
in Area B.
(He bet a 5 on Area B.)
I won another one.
Do you think other people
will have a 5 in Round 5?
I don't think so.
They obviously used all of them.
I knew I'd win that area
the moment I placed a five.
It was insane. The evil second baseman.
He hit a home run every time
he was at bat. How is that possible?
A batter should wait to see...
if it's a ball or a strike.
But he hit a home run
every time he swung that bat.
I just...
couldn't compete.
Keun Woo is on a roll.
He's so good.
Area C goes to Hye Seon.
They could get in your way.
(Ji Hoo sighing)
We lost the reverse card,
which went to Team P3.
I was in danger.
Area D goes to YunB.
Nice.
How is Keun Woo so good at this?
- It makes no sense.
- That's awesome.
Jeez.
I won 4 out of 5 times.
That's incredible.
I'm reading your mind like an open book.
(Round 5 Betting Results)
(Ji Hoo 2, Keun Woo 5, Hye Seon 3, YunB 3)
You will now place your movement cards.
Hye Seon, please place your cards.
It looks like Keun Woo is joining them.
Are you and Keun Woo close?
- No.
- Not at all?
Why do you ask?
Doesn't it look like he's joining them?
What's your plan, Keun Woo?
- What?
- What's your plan?
I'm torn.
- What do you mean?
- I'm trying to decide.
I usually go straight in real life,
but I occasionally want
to take the scenic route.
It does feel good...
- to win 4 out of 5 bids.
- I know, right?
How did you bet
exactly the right amount every time?
That's so cool.
What are you going to do?
I can't decide.
Aren't you going to go forward?
Me?
I should.
Or you could give it to me.
Then...
- What I'm saying is...
- I think...
Could we ask Keun Woo to put this here?
Four?
That's not bad.
It was 25 percent, right?
- That one.
- What?
Get that yellow car out of the way.
- Whose car is it?
- YunB's.
Oh, it's YunB's?
And we'll take the blue one down.
He's too far ahead.
But the blue one isn't trying to go.
- He didn't have a chance.
- He just couldn't.
We crashed into him earlier.
I had to go as slowly as possible,
so I couldn't decide...
whether to turn it over, stop other cars,
or collide with them.
- Just...
- Who should I give the reverse to?
It's obvious.
Place it on the right side
of Ji Hoo's slot.
Ji Hoo is too far ahead of us.
Too far ahead.
(The reverse card goes to Ji Hoo.)
(Placing a 0 and a 3
in Seong Beom's slots)
Jeong Keun Woo, please place your cards.
Okay.
We can't have someone pull ahead
early in the game.
- Are you serious, Keun Woo?
- Yes.
You'll really do it?
- Go away.
- Will you really do it?
Let's see.
You'll...
Can you at least reduce it to two?
Reduce it to two...
(He places a 4 in Ji Hoo's slot.)
Nice.
I begged him, but he still placed a four.
The Majority Alliance I was worried about
has formed.
If they keep pulling me back
by 4 or 3 spaces,
I could be in real trouble.
In my mind, I still feel like...
the skin is nearer than the shirt.
I tried to help Team P3...
with their strategies a bit.
Let's see.
You could move it here.
You could give it to YunB or Hye Seon.
Anything would be fine.
YunB is having a fright.
He's scared of heights.
- What?
- You're scared of heights, YunB.
(YunB's car is on top of Jin Ho's car.)
Seung Yong.
Too bad.
(He places it in YunB's slot.)
You guys suddenly come to me
and butter me up.
You guys...
I felt like I became rich.
They came to me to ask a favor and so on.
This is nothing to me,
so I can place the cards...
without much thought.
I just did it thinking about
Tae Gyun and Ji Min who had to leave.
Kang Ji Hoo, please place your cards.
In this case, there's nothing we can do.
Right.
We need to wait for the others
to move first.
Let's make this a total mess.
Two and three?
- Two and three?
- Yes.
- To you?
Okay. I'll do this.
Where should I place a one?
Me.
- Should I?
- Give it to Hye Seon.
We'll return you one next time.
Let's do that.
- How about Keun Woo?
- What do you want?
I don't want anything.
Just discard it.
Seriously.
Give it to me.
I'm at the starting line.
- This looks fine.
- If Seong Beom leaves, I'll be alone.
(He places the cards
in Seung Yong and Sung Joo's slots.)
- One, two, three.
- You are so mean.
YunB, please place your cards.
Should I push Jin Ho to the left?
With 1 and 3?
Who's moving first?
Jin Ho...
Since this is Round Six...
Good. You need to move first though.
(Jin Ho's car can't move
no matter what card they put in his slot.)
- That's a good idea.
- Like this.
(He places a 3 and a 1 in Jin Ho's slots.)
Two...
You could put a two in Sung Joo's slot.
Since Sung Joo plays alone,
he'd have predicted himself lower.
(He places the remaining card
in Sung Joo's slot.)
All the movement cards have been placed.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
(Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom, Jin Ho,
Sung Joo, and Seung Yong can move.)
The race cars will start moving now.
Hong Jin Ho. You cannot move.
Too bad.
You can't move anyway.
Mine will be gone anyway.
I miscalculated.
I thought we were in Round Six.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Hyun Sung Joo,
1 space forward and 1 space left.
You're pulling ahead.
An underdog's rebellion.
Shin Seung Yong, 2 spaces forward
and 1 space right.
- Yes.
- So chummy.
Kang Ji Hoo, four spaces backward.
Yes, I'm in the lead.
YunB is racing fast.
Showing my intention to win...
might prove to be a bad mistake.
I resented Keun Woo.
YunB is racing fast.
- Isn't that a slipstream for YunB?
- You're right.
It is.
YunB wanted to stay behind.
YunB, booster activated.
You will start two spaces ahead.
One space forward and one space right.
(YunB takes the lead.)
It's not bad, actually.
I have no idea how it's going to go.
Me too. It's so difficult.
- It's completely different from just now.
- You need to factor in many things...
because you need to move others' cars too.
Right. This is fun.
Heo Seong Beom, three spaces right.
Ouch.
Flip over.
You've collided with the wall.
(Seong Beom's race car flipped over.)
Your race car has flipped over,
and you cannot move until the next round.
Okay.
I couldn't exactly go anywhere
with the other players around,
so I decided to crash into the wall.
When I do, I can't reverse either.
I can skip one round
without anyone messing with me.
So I decided to let it go...
and think about the next move.
(Round 5 Movement Results)
(Player, predicted rank)
(YunB, Sung Joo, Seung Yong, Ji Hoo,)
(Keun Woo, Jin Ho, Seong Beom, Hye Seon)
Goodness.
Seong Beom might've predicted himself
as a lower rank.
He wouldn't make
such an obvious mistake otherwise.
It's definitely not a mistake.
He moved 2 spaces forward
and will take a break for 1 round.
And Sung Joo definitely didn't
predict himself to be in first place.
- No.
- It'll be good...
to make him first place.
Seong Beom might've predicted himself
a lower rank,
but not 7th or 8th place, I think.
So we could put him in that rank.
Let's see.
This is interesting.
What a nice, fun mess.
Keun Woo said he predicted sixth place.
That overlaps with me.
Heo Seong Beom,
choose your predicted rank.
I choose sixth.
I have a good feeling about it.
(Heo Seong Beom's predicted rank is 6th.)
(Keun Woo and Seong Beom talked
before placing the movement cards.)
I chose a lower rank.
I predicted myself as sixth.
(Seong Beom has the same predicted rank
as Keun Woo.)
He overlaps with you.
That explains why he's playing like that.
Yes.
Before Round Six starts,
the hidden rule will be revealed.
The hidden rule of Prediction Race is
changing the predictions.
After Round Six ends,
the player with the lowest rank...
can change their predicted rank once.
- Only the lowest rank? Who is it?
- Only the lowest rank?
(Currently in last place
is Choi Hye Seon.)
(4 candidates of the hidden rule)
(Heo Seong Beom, Hong Jin Ho,
Choi Hye Seon, Jeong Keun Woo)
It means nothing
unless you're in last place.
Change it?
Round Six will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Hye Seon)
- They'll give us new betting cards.
- Yes.
I can't move in this round.
Jeong Keun Woo, here is your betting card.
Thank you.
You've placed Card Four in Area D.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
- I want to...
- You can do that.
I want to take Area B.
- Area B?
- Yes.
It's easier for you to move that way.
I don't think...
people will bet this round aggressively.
Keun Woo already went inside.
We'll lose the moment we bet
on the same area as Keun Woo.
- He's really good at betting.
- How does betting a four on Area B sound?
Four on Area B?
We have time.
Let's think about it more together.
Yes, let's take it slow.
A isn't bad, but...
Which area will you choose?
I'll discard the lower one.
Shall we play this round individually?
So nobody knows what will happen.
I don't move first,
so I don't need to risk it by going to C.
I think B is the safe option.
Shin Seung Yong.
You've placed Card One in Area D.
Kang Ji Hoo.
You've placed Card One in Area C.
YunB. You've placed Card One in Area B.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
I bet a one on B.
They'll get in the way of
whoever they want, so it's pointless.
Seong Beom has very sharp ears.
- We need to speak softer.
- What?
Seong Beom has very sharp ears,
so we need to speak softer.
- And don't use gestures.
- Okay.
What will you do?
- What?
- What will you do?
My head hurts.
Listening to me won't help you anyway.
He's bluffing again.
Hyun Sung Joo.
You've placed Card Five in Area A.
Keun Woo. I'll lose
if I bet on the same area as you.
So just tell me which area I should avoid.
You might lose real bad.
I'll avoid that area.
I'll do this.
Choi Hye Seon.
You've placed Card Two in Area B.
I'll go big.
- Four.
- Hong Jin Ho.
You've placed Card Four in Area C.
Heo Seong Beom.
You've placed Card One in Area C.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
Area A goes to Hyun Sung Joo.
Area B goes to...
- Choi Hye Seon.
- Yes.
What? Lucky her.
Area C goes to Hong Jin Ho.
I actually got this?
Area D goes to Jeong Keun Woo.
You're incredible, Keun Woo.
Seriously.
Goodness.
What's happening?
He's a deity.
How did you do it?
Do I stink?
Do you avoid the areas I bet on?
- This is ridiculous.
- You're amazing.
- Do I stink?
- This is impossible.
It's as expected.
I'm the king of successful bids.
They started buzzing.
I didn't simply bid.
What cards are useless to them...
but useful to me?
- My gosh.
- You will now...
place your movement cards.
(Placing the movement cards)
Choi Hye Seon, please place your cards.
(Round 6, Hye Seon, Sung Joo,
Keun Woo, Jin Ho)
Look.
What move will be the best?
You can move forward. Do you want to?
Yes, it doesn't matter.
- What's that?
- Should we move Ji Hoo...
right or left?
(Kang Ji Hoo)
- Right is better.
- Right is better, right?
- Yes.
- Then we'll do this.
Nice.
It's about time we move things around
to suit our needs.
Why don't we stop hiding...
and make our moves aggressively?
Sorry, Ji Hoo.
- Where should I place three?
- Should I go?
- You can go.
- We can do 1 and 3, right?
- Then you can pull ahead.
- Yes.
(Choi Hye Seon, 1, 3)
I'm no longer in last place.
(Round 6, Hye Seon, Sung Joo,
Keun Woo, Jin Ho)
In Round Six, Hye Seon placed...
zero on my right slot.
Which means she wants me to flip over
to the left.
I was very grateful for it.
I want to flip over.
That way, they can't make me go backward.
I'm so glad.
I can flip over and defend one round.
Where will you place yours?
- What?
- Where will you place yours?
Hye Seon needs to place hers first.
Once she's done,
I can see which slots are still available.
The outer line means last place.
They're making Seong Beom place last.
You're very confident in your predictions.
How cocky.
I used to be like that.
Should I help or not?
I'll just do my own thing.
Is there a way?
I'll do my thing.
(Hyun Sung Joo, 2, 1)
I can't tell
how the game is going to play out.
You now have one minute left.
(Round 6, Hye Seon, Sung Joo,
Keun Woo, Jin Ho)
(Hyun Sung Joo discards Movement Card 2.)
- What did he discard?
- Two.
- Three.
- Wasn't it two?
(Round 6, Hye Seon, Sung Joo,
Keun Woo, Jin Ho)
I discarded two.
Let's see.
It's my turn, right?
Jeong Keun Woo, please place your cards.
My gosh.
(Jeong Keun Woo, 1 and reverse)
What?
You want to place last?
(Round 6, Hye Seon, Sung Joo,
Keun Woo, Jin Ho)
No. I'm going to cause a ruckus.
Please help me.
It's meaningless anyway.
I'll change everything.
You take it, Jin Ho.
(He places Movement Card 3
in Jin Ho's R slot.)
Hong Jin Ho, please place your cards.
I'll think about who I should give
the remaining cards to.
For now...
Place yours first.
We have three minutes to think.
Jin Ho, you have a three in your slot.
(His friend Keun Woo placed a 3
in his slot.)
(Round 6, Hye Seon, Sung Joo,
Keun Woo, Jin Ho)
Keun Woo. Did you help me?
- No.
- Or do you hate me?
I wanted to add variables
to your calculations.
He decided my moves for me.
- Yes.
- You...
Don't offend me, or you'll all die.
I won 5 out of 6 bids.
Darn it.
You guys... There are so many variables.
(Round 6, Hye Seon, Sung Joo,
Keun Woo, Jin Ho)
(Hong Jin Ho, L and 3)
(Hong Jin Ho, 4, 3)
What will you do?
- Discard?
- Me?
Seung Yong? YunB?
Discard!
What's wrong with you?
Get you a bit excited.
I almost got excited.
This is fun.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
All the movement cards have been placed.
The race cars will start moving now.
I can't tell how they'll change.
(Race cars start moving.)
Choi Hye Seon, one space forward...
and two spaces right.
There.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
Hyun Sung Joo, one space forward,
and one space left.
He's pulling ahead.
Yes.
Jeong Keun Woo, one space backward.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
Hong Jin Ho, booster activated.
You will start two spaces ahead.
Three spaces forward, and one space left.
(Hyun Sung Joo)
What would you like, Sung Joo?
Should I move or stay?
- Do whatever you want.
- Whatever I want?
You've collided with Sung Joo's race car.
I wasn't targeting Sung Joo specifically.
He was just on the way.
So I got on his car.
You can't plan this ahead...
because you need to see
how others arrange the orders...
and how the cars move.
You can't plan ahead.
That's just how the game is.
All players have completed their moves.
(Round 6 movements completed)
Next round onward,
Heo Seong Beom's race car can move.
- Hurrah.
- Good for you.
Jeong Keun Woo,
who is in last place for Round Six,
can change your predicted rank.
The predicted rank...
You need to change it, right?
- I can change it however I want, right?
- Yes.
Was today's hidden rule made for Keun Woo?
"The hidden rule.
The person in last place..."
"can change their predicted rank."
When I heard that,
I decided to win the bid,
use a reverse card, become last place,
and change my predicted rank.
Jeong Keun Woo.
Will you change your predicted rank?
I'll change it to seventh place.
When I'm in 7th place,
I just need to be mindful of 8th place.
But when I'm in 6th place, I need to keep
both 7th and 8th places in check.
So I planned to move one space backward...
and change my predicted rank
to seventh place.
(Round 7, Sung Joo)
Round Seven will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
This is really hard.
I can't predict what will happen at all.
Sung Joo finds this situation
uncomfortable.
- I'm happy.
- Jin Ho needs to move.
I'll do what I can.
(Sung Joo's car is under Jin Ho's.)
Sung Joo resents Jin Ho yet again today.
I've never resented him.
I was grateful yesterday,
and I'm grateful today.
It's my turn. I'll start.
Where did you bet on?
- I'll avoid you.
- Area D.
I used a low card. No need to go big now.
It's not necessary yet.
(YunB wants to save up
on his betting cards.)
I'll stay still.
- Do you want to move forward?
- Yes.
If you don't move,
my booster will be activated.
- I'll move no matter what.
- You'll move no matter what?
- No matter what.
- Don't stop me.
- And...
Hye Seon will step on you.
Poor Ji Hoo. Is he crying?
Ji Hoo... A cheetah always smiles.
It can run later.
How philosophical.
Let's sit.
We need to plan.
We have no time to waste.
Which cards should we get? They...
If you were them,
which cards would you go for?
I think they'll go for B or C.
One of us could go
for a less competitive area,
and two could bet on the same area...
to support one of us.
Like what we did just now.
I'll bet a one on this.
Later, as we get closer to Round Ten,
we'll need cards with higher numbers.
Everyone seems to be saving up
on higher cards.
We need to use Card One sooner or later,
so we'll have to give up on one round.
We don't have a choice.
Seung Yong went 2nd in Round 7,
so he could lead the bets.
It was a very important moment.
Shin Seung Yong.
You've placed Card Four in Area B.
Seung Yong bet Card Four,
and I discarded my card.
Kang Ji Hoo.
You've placed Card Two in Area A.
You look relaxed.
- Sorry?
- You look relaxed.
Right?
It's fascinating.
How did I win all the bids?
- It is pretty fascinating.
- Right?
It's impossible.
I'm playing all by myself,
and I won 5 out of 6 bids.
Sometimes,
thinking too much doesn't help.
Yes.
A straightforward approach
works best sometimes.
Here are the betting results
of each area in Round Seven.
(Round 7 Betting Results)
Area A has no winners.
You will now place your movement cards.
Shin Seung Yong, please place your cards.
What will you do?
If you look at this...
If you don't move,
you'll be moved three spaces backward.
Hold on.
Whatever card I use on you,
you'll flip over.
I think that's better.
You want that?
Seung Yong made me flip over
to the left with Card Four.
And he moved forward using 2 pieces
of Card 2.
Seung Yong is pulling ahead.
Heo Seong Beom, please place your cards.
We can use this together
because we're next to each other.
You can do as you like.
The attack...
If you use a three...
Here's Seung Yong and here's Ji Hoo.
(The spaces Seung Yong and Ji Hoo
will move to)
Or you can get on top of Seung Yong's car.
- I can do that.
- Yes, you can.
Should I do that?
(Hye Seon can collide into Seung Yong
by using Seong Beom and Jin Ho's Card 3s.)
Using 2 Card 3s?
I'll go this way.
Two and one.
- You get it, right?
- Okay.
You now have one minute left.
I'll do that.
- Okay.
You have 30 seconds left.
Who wants to reverse?
Seung Yong.
You want to reverse, Seung Yong?
There's no slot left.
Time's up.
It's discarded.
(Heo Seong Beom's reverse card
is discarded.)
Hong Jin Ho, please place your cards.
Then...
That one.
If you don't have a card, go away.
Hye Seon...
Hye Seon is racing fast.
Move forward.
You've already discussed beforehand.
We're double-checking.
I will just...
- Watch your mouth.
- Please.
I only moved two spaces...
in three hours. Don't touch me.
Give me one.
- What?
- I can't move anyway.
No.
Sung Joo can't move anyway.
You can't move unless I do.
But I don't plan to move.
Why?
Or give it to YunB.
YunB feels upset at being left out.
But he has no plans to move.
Like this. Go big.
(He places 0 in YunB's slot.)
Go big.
You won't give it to your friend.
It's a bad card.
- It's a bad card?
- It's a bad card.
It's a bad card?
Seriously.
All the movement cards have been placed.
(Ji Hoo, Seong Beom, Hye Seon,
and Seung Yong can move.)
The race cars will start moving now.
(Race cars start moving.)
Shin Seung Yong, two spaces forward.
Yes.
Kang Ji Hoo, four spaces left.
You've collided into the wall.
Your race car has flipped over,
and you cannot move until the next round.
Heo Seong Beom, one space forward,
and one space left.
Does it mean
Hye Seon activates her booster?
Get on my back.
Choi Hye Seon, booster activated.
You will start two spaces ahead.
Get on Seung Yong's back.
Three spaces forward.
- Get on it.
- Vroom.
- You've collided...
- It's carpool.
with Seung Yong's race car.
Oh, my gosh.
- We move forward regardless.
- All players have...
- How fascinating.
- completed their moves.
- This is interesting.
- Right?
Things are getting interesting.
Let's go win the bid.
Round Eight will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Round 8, Seung Yong)
Things are starting to get harder.
I'm getting a headache.
I'm so envious of Keun Woo.
For us,
it doesn't really matter...
- if we make a move or not.
- Right.
They're the ones who need to start moving.
They must be discussing...
whether to defend the reverse card or not.
Hye Seon, Seong Beom, and Jin Ho.
I still can't figure out...
who predicted higher rank
and who predicted lower.
- What do you think?
- Sorry?
What do you think?
I'm not sure either.
But...
Seong Beom must've predicted
2nd, 3rd, or 4th place.
I think that's what he'll do,
given his personality.
The typical move would be...
Seong Beom and Jin Ho
predicting higher ranks...
and Hye Seon predicting a lower rank.
I think it's their typical move.
But seeing how Hye Seon is pulling ahead,
I'm starting to think I might be wrong.
They're probably doing what we're doing.
They don't play aggressively at first
to fool the others...
and...
Either the ranks early in the game
are not important,
or they're making strange moves
to hide their intentions.
That's why the last round is important
for me.
It's not bad for Rounds 18 and 19
because YunB and I are the 1st players.
But I'm worried about this.
(He's worried that the 1st player for
Round 20, the final round, is Seong Beom.)
We must stop them in this round.
For now, I'll stay as neutral as I can...
and support you if I can.
At the end,
it's best to work with YunB.
I'll get going.
Here are the betting results
of each area in Round Eight.
(Round 8 Betting Results)
The winners are spread out evenly.
Let's see what we can do.
I have no idea what's going to happen.
I'll support you until mid-to-late game,
so help me just once later in the game.
You bet.
You will now place your movement cards.
Shin Seung Yong, please place your cards.
Nyom nyom.
Do allow me to move now.
I've been parked for too long.
Right. You need to get rid of Hye Seon.
- Waste of fuel...
- Why get rid of me?
From Seung Yong's perspective, I mean.
That's right.
- I will...
- Wise choice.
send YunB forward
and make Keun Woo's ranking go up.
(Jeong Keun Woo, 2, 3)
(YunB, 0, 1)
My gosh.
Keun Woo's choices are gone.
You've ruined...
my plan.
Jeong Keun Woo, please place your cards.
I want to move forward too.
I was thinking about that.
That looks good.
Let's go with 3 and 3.
I'm thinking of doing that
and messing up the whole thing.
- Three collisions.
- Three burgers?
- Three burgers.
- Not there.
- Two and three look nice too.
- Why're you doing this?
- Let's go with 3 and 3.
- Why?
- No.
- Move Hye Seon and Jin Ho.
Keun Woo, I need a three too.
- Hold on.
- I could make use of the three.
- Everyone.
- You guys.
- Today's key is Keun Woo.
- Hold on.
You demand the cards from me...
without giving me a single cent.
You demand and take everything...
from me.
He's become the joker.
Sung Joo, do you want to advance?
- I can't.
- He can't.
That's why I'm giving it to you.
(Hyun Sung Joo, L and 2)
You're just giving it to him?
- You have one minute left.
- Okay.
(Choi Hye Seon, L and 3)
Okay.
Make Seong Beom reverse?
Kang Ji Hoo, please place your cards.
Jin Ho or Seong Beom.
Who's better?
Seong Beom?
We got very lucky...
when a three was placed
in Seong Beom's slot.
I could place a reverse card next to it...
and send him back three spaces.
Had Keun Woo not placed a three
in Seong Beom's slot,
I could have only made him go back
two spaces with the cards I had.
I was really happy
I could send him back three spaces.
It's not a bad idea to send
Seong Beom back using the reverse card.
I'm going to do that.
- Here?
- I'll put this here.
(Heo Seong Beom, 3 and reverse)
- Reverse and a three?
- Yes.
I'm moving backward.
- Should I discard this?
- Or Hye Seon?
We can make them collide.
- You have ten seconds left.
- We can flip it over.
- Just discard it.
- Don't do this.
Gosh, you're...
- so mean.
- Kang Ji Hoo, you've discarded a card.
This is fun.
At this point,
it's just a personal grudge.
He just hates me.
And I think...
the reverse card is very important
in playing Prediction Race.
And he used it on me,
which was a wrong move.
It's that team's mistake,
but I could see it clearly,
which made it more fun.
I could feel the hostility.
Choi Hye Seon, please place your cards.
Should I stay on your back forever?
- Should I stay...
- Me?
on your back forever?
Just scrap it.
Should I just stay there?
I think we should put a zero here.
- Seung Yong?
- Yes.
We have no use for a zero.
- You have no use...
- I can discard it.
- for a zero,
- It's unnecessary.
but if you're going to discard it,
it's better to place it there.
- As a gift.
- Why are you doing this to me?
I'll increase your chance...
- of getting flipped over.
- I let you go...
earlier.
- Then...
- YunB will go like this.
Then you get your booster on.
So you can take off.
Isn't it better that way?
You're right.
Ta-da.
Jin Ho can move one space.
Jin Ho, do you want to move
and let Sung Joo go?
Sung Joo...
Don't move me.
- You don't want to?
- No.
- Discard it.
(Choi Hye Seon discards Movement Card 1.)
All the movement cards have been placed.
The race cars will start moving now.
Jeong Keun Woo, two spaces forward...
and one space right.
Vroom.
- We've come a long way in three hours.
- We sure have.
YunB, one space right.
Heo Seong Beom, three spaces backward.
Thank you.
When you made it this far.
Choi Hye Seon, booster activated.
You will start two spaces ahead.
- You're pulling ahead.
- Nice, right?
Yes, it's a long way to London.
Three spaces forward and one space left.
That's so far ahead.
- You're like Usain Bolt.
- The distance between us is crazy.
Oh, dear.
- You're like Usain Bolt.
- It's like the sky and the ground.
- She's so far ahead.
- How to catch up?
I feel proud.
(Round 8 Movement Results)
(Player, predicted rank:
1. Choi Hye Seon, 2. YunB,)
(3. Hong Jin Ho, 4. Hyun Sung Joo,
5. Shin Seung Yong, 6. Kang Ji Ho,)
(7. Jeong Keun Woo, 8. Heo Seong Beom)
Round Nine starts now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Round 9, Keun Woo starts 1st.)
(Jeong Keun Woo plays 1st in Round 9.)
(Once again, he heads straight
to the Voting Room.)
(Jeong Keun Woo bets a 3 on an Area.)
You've placed Card Three.
The game was so easy.
(The situation makes him whistle.)
(Singing)
(He even feels a bit bored.)
The cards for Round Nine were revealed.
Reverse and a four came up together.
(Ji Hoo is currently in 6th place,
his predicted rank being 2nd.)
(Kang Ji Hoo)
It won't be easy
if they try to pull me back.
I must win the bid.
(Seung Yong's remaining cards,
Ji Hoo's remaining cards)
I'll bet a five on Area C.
(Nodding)
Shin Seung Yong, place a card
in the area of your choosing.
(Shin Seung Yong bets a 5 on Area C.)
In case it doesn't work out,
you should bet a 3 or a 4 on Area C.
- To the same area?
- Yes.
Since Hye Seon is pulling too far ahead,
we could send her four spaces backward.
(Hye Seon is leading with a big gap.)
(Choi Hye Seon)
I think this is better.
What's the reason?
Because I think they'll want to win this.
This isn't too bad either.
We could just be wasting
our betting cards.
They could attack you with this.
Anyway,
we must stop Hye Seon.
- We must win Area C.
- You'll do it?
I bet a five on Area C,
but it'll definitely become null.
So I'd like you to bet a 4 or a 3
on Area C.
But I don't know which is better.
- I think we need both 4 and 3.
- What?
We need to bet both 4 and 3.
That doesn't sound bad.
(Seung Yong Alliance plans
to secure Area C by playing safe.)
Do you have a 3 or a 4?
I have a four.
(YunB's remaining cards)
Can you bet a four on Area C?
A four on Area C?
So we'll bet a 3, a 4, and a 5.
I don't think they'll bet that eagerly
on Area C.
I think they will.
Shall we talk over there?
(Kang Ji Hoo, predicted rank, 2nd place)
- Yes.
- They will...
definitely bet a 5 and a 4 on Area C.
You're 100 percent sure?
(Nodding)
Okay, then.
I'll bet a four on Area C.
(Kang Ji Hoo bets a 3 on Area C.)
It means I need to counter them...
and you need to back me up.
(Team P3 Alliance also comes up with
a backup plan...)
(in case their votes become null.)
(Choi Hye Seon has placed her bet.)
(Heo Seong Beom has placed his bet.)
(All the players have placed their bets.)
I will announce the betting results.
(Round 9 Betting Results)
Area A goes to Choi Hye Seon.
Area B goes to Heo Seong Beom.
Area C goes to Shin Seung Yong.
Area D goes to Jeong Keun Woo.
You're seriously...
You're a master. You win every round.
Didn't he win almost every round?
Did you rig it?
(Round 9 Betting Results)
(A, Choi Hye Seon, B, Heo Seong Beom,
C, Shin Seung Yong, D, Jeong Keun Woo)
(Team P3 Alliance did not bet on Area C.)
I think it was a wrong move.
We just wasted a four.
What are you guys doing?
We secured the reverse card as planned,
but the opposing alliance won
all the other three bids.
Even if Hye Seon pulls ahead,
you won't keep going.
They'll focus on Hye Seon
to try and stop her.
It's not bad, actually.
Choi Hye Seon, choose your predicted rank.
You predicted you would be in third place.
(Choi Hye Seon's predicted rank is
3rd place.)
If I pull ahead from the start,
I could become a target,
or someone could get on top of my car.
Or I could unintentionally serve
as a booster for someone else.
So I'll pull ahead as a test
or as a bluff,
and they'll follow behind me
while I act as a shield.
That was our strategy.
(She's playing the tank role
of the alliance.)
They could attack you with this.
What's the point of sending me back?
It's not bad for me, though.
I knew how important a reverse card was.
It's much easier to make
unconventional moves with it.
But, despite that,
if we could win two areas
and get six cards,
we could use them to defend ourselves.
You will now place your movement cards.
(Placing movement cards)
Jeong Keun Woo, please place your cards.
(The first player is Jeong Keun Woo.)
(Round 9, Keun Woo, Seong Beom,
Hye Seon, Seung Yong)
(Placing)
My gosh.
(Kang Ji Hoo, currently in 6th place)
(He will become 3rd place at once.)
(3rd place)
You're really changing the whole game.
I can't predict your moves.
You all are dead today.
(He places the remaining 3
in Heo Seong Beom's slot.)
Are you including me in this race?
- You're way behind.
- That's right.
- He's way behind.
- You're way behind.
(He placed the movement cards evenly
to both alliances.)
He let me get on top of Jin Ho,
who is on top of Sung Joo,
to the third level.
He made the best move for me.
He set me back four spaces earlier,
and now,
he's sending me three spaces forward.
What is this? I can't understand him.
It felt like
Keun Woo was part of the game too.
I can't understand
how he wins all the bids either.
Him pulling me back and pushing me forward
makes me think...
he's maintaining the balance of the game.
Today, I'll be a bass.
It was my goal...
to make the game muddy...
so I could stay behind.
Heo Seong Beom, please place your cards.
(Seong Beom needs to place a card
bigger than 2.)
Jin Ho, you need to move forward.
He can't move.
Ji Hoo took this card.
- He goes first.
- I...
- No.
- Ji Hoo goes first.
Give me one to reset that.
- Need to get rid of it.
- Reset it.
Any card.
(Round 9, Keun Woo, Seong Beom,
Hye Seon, Seung Yong)
(He places Cards 3 and 1 as planned.)
What about Hye Seon?
She needs to move.
You want to move Hye Seon? Should I?
- I can go.
- Isn't it better if she goes?
- Okay.
- I'm unrivaled,
- I'll give you a left.
- so I doubt anyone can catch me.
(He places the last 3 he has
in Hye Seon's slot.)
Choi Hye Seon, please place your cards.
(Choi Hye Seon's turn)
(Hye Seon fills up her gear board
to defend from a reverse card.)
- What happened?
- Stopping that from using the booster.
- Who?
- You.
- Me?
- Yes.
(Seung Yong can activate the booster,
as he is right behind YunB.)
(Shin Seung Yong)
I'll flip over YunB.
(She places 0 and 2 in YunB's slots.)
(Lastly, it's Shin Seung Yong's turn.)
- It's not too bad.
- What?
Shall we aim for the next turn?
We got really good cards,
a reverse card and a four.
But we couldn't use them.
They'd filled up all their slots.
(Round 9, Keun Woo, Seong Beom,
Hye Seon, Seung Yong)
(He voids the reverse
and places 1 on his slot.)
(Round 9, Keun Woo, Seong Beom,
Hye Seon, Seung Yong)
(He places 4 in Jeong Keun Woo's slot.)
We were sure Keun Woo's predicted rank
was low,
so we placed a four in Keun Woo's slot
to send him forward.
Thank you. I thought I'd be
the only one left out.
But you gave me one.
All the movement cards have been placed.
(Round 9)
(Everyone except Jeong Keun Woo can move.)
The race cars will start moving now.
Kang Ji Hoo,
1 space forward and 1 space right.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
You've collided with Sung Joo's
and Jin Ho's race cars.
Hamburger.
- Hamburger.
- Three-storey.
This is the first three-storey collision.
Let's sleep here.
YunB, two spaces right.
Your race car has flipped over,
and you cannot move until the next round.
Heo Seong Beom, three spaces forward.
I'm finally back to my original spot.
Choi Hye Seon,
2 spaces forward and 1 space left.
- Let's go, Hye Seon.
- Let's go.
Here she goes.
(Hye Seon has widened the gap.)
So this is how it feels.
I want to come in first place.
Same here.
Hyun Sung Joo. You cannot move.
(There's a long way for Sung Joo to go.)
I'd better grab some grub.
Shin Seung Yong, one space right.
(Seung Yong is back
to where he could get a booster.)
What?
Hold on. I practically helped him
get a booster.
Smart move, Seung Yong.
All players have completed their moves.
(Round 9 Movement Results)
(Player, predicted rank:
1. Choi Hye Seon, 2. YunB,)
(3. Shin Seung Yong, 4. Kang Ji Hoo,
5. Hong Jin Ho, 6. Hyun Sung Joo,)
(7. Jeong Keun Woo, 8. Heo Seong Beom)
We will begin Round Ten.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,)
(Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
(Staring)
It's not moving at all. It's not.
It's not moving.
(Sung Joo has been buried since Round 6.)
I'll get rid of them...
if I win an area.
Hi.
You've placed Card Three in Area D.
Is that right?
Yes.
(Sung Joo dreams of winning.)
Please move to the main hall.
- It's you, right?
- What? Yes.
We should both check.
(Ji Hoo and YunB are the first to start.)
Either of us needs to win.
From what I see,
Hye Seon in a commanding lead is...
actually great.
Either way, you're 2nd place
and I'm 3rd place.
Aside from Ji Hoo and me,
someone on the other team...
had to be in first place,
whether it was Hye Seon or someone else.
But it ended up being Hye Seon.
(YunB: Predicted 3rd,
Kang Ji Hoo: Predicted 2nd)
(YunB and Ji Hoo are leading,
just as predicted.)
No one was coming in first place.
But thanks to Hye Seon moving forward,
I can act as if I wanted to follow her.
With that,
I can naturally come in second place.
I'm in a way better place than before.
How about letting Hye Seon go?
Why?
I don't mind.
But I'm worried she'd go too far.
The other team is trying to end the game.
(The game ends
when a player finishes the race.)
We can adjust our team's pace,
but not theirs.
I currently have Three,
so I think you or YunB...
should go for 4 or 5.
I personally think 4 is better of the 2.
(The goal is Area D,
where the reverse is.)
(YunB bets a 5 on Area D.)
(Kang Ji Hoo bets a 4 on Area A.)
(Shin Seung Yong bets a 3 on Area B.)
(Seung Yong Alliance
shares the betting information.)
Just look at them.
- So...
- Yes?
You're willing to betray...
if you ever get in a favorable situation
in the far future, right?
Of course.
- Yes?
- Yes.
If we split up...
and can't win together,
I'll secure my win.
It's risky,
so I'm not going to share anything.
Right.
- Sung Joo...
- I'm watching with full attention.
Are you confident about
not telling anyone?
Of course.
I'll tell you in a bit.
There's no need to tell me now.
If we need to talk in the later half,
you have to find me.
After all, I'm alone.
Me looking for you is weird.
Here's what's clear. I'm in the lead.
That's obvious
even without you telling me.
Okay.
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
Area A has no winners.
That's bad.
Area B goes to Shin Seung Yong.
(Area B goes to Shin Seung Yong.)
Area C goes to Choi Hye Seon.
Area D goes to YunB.
(Round 10 Betting Results)
(A: Kang Ji Hoo, Heo Seong Beom,
B: Shin Seung Yong,)
(C: Choi Hye Seon, Hong Jin Ho,
D: YunB, Hyun Sung Joo, Jeong Keun Woo)
You will now place your movement cards.
YunB, please place your cards.
(Placing reverse and 3
without a 2nd thought)
- What?
- We've been attacked.
He's dragging us down.
- Hye Seon?
- Don't do this.
I couldn't help but wonder
why they're pulling...
Hye Seon back.
I doubt there was a first place.
Did Ji Hoo really write down first place?
Letting Hye Seon get first place is
favorable to us.
There was no need to pull her back.
But I had to keep acting out
the image that...
I'm striving to come in first place.
Acting as if
I wanted to come in first place.
Acting like I'm going to pull
Hye Seon back.
All the movement cards have been placed.
(Round 10: Jeong Keun Woo, Kang Ji Hoo,
Heo Seong Beom, Choi Hye Seon)
The race cars will start moving now.
Kang Ji Hoo, 2 spaces forward
and 1 space right.
One, two, three.
(Ji Hoo pulls far ahead.)
Heo Seong Beom, 1 space forward
and 1 space right.
Three cars.
Choi Hye Seon, three spaces backward.
- Seriously?
- Look at the gap now.
You guys are right on my heels.
Jeong Keun Woo, 2 spaces forward
and 1 space left.
Crash!
- No.
- A three-stack burger.
You've collided with Hyun Sung Joo
and Hong Jin Ho's...
- race cars.
- A three-stack burger.
Jin Ho can't escape.
I'm doomed.
- A three-stack burger.
- YunB, your car can move now.
(Round 10 Movement Results)
(Player, predicted rank:
1. Choi Hye Seon, 2. Kang Ji Hoo,)
(3. YunB, 4. Shin Seung Yong,
5. Heo Seong Beom, 6. Jeong Keun Woo,)
(7. Hong Jin Ho, 8. Hyun Sung Joo)
Sung Joo, hang in there.
You'll be able to move soon.
That's been on my mind for the past hour.
(A three-stack burger parking:)
(Jeong Keun Woo, Hong Jin Ho,
Hyun Sung Joo)
Sung Joo...
- Don't you pity him?
- I do.
Sung Joo is being crushed by everyone.
- Should I help you out, Sung Joo?
- What?
Do you need my help?
Are you okay being crushed down?
It won't go your way either way.
Why not?
There's another player on top.
He needs to move...
- as well.
- If I make a move out,
you'll be able to get the car out
on the next turn.
You kept winning the bets,
so I doubt you will this time.
Isn't it a new round now?
Isn't it Round 11?
- Yes.
- You're right.
He's the king of betting.
(A new round receiving new betting cards)
Round 11 will begin now.
(Round 11)
(Jeong Keun Woo, Kang Ji Hoo, YunB,
Heo Seong Beom, Hong Jin Ho,)
(Choi Hye Seon, Hyun Sung Joo,
Shin Seung Yong)
- Tell me something, Keun Woo.
- What?
Are you going to go backward or not?
If possible.
I am!
(Keun Woo is after the reverse card.)
You're in front of everyone, no?
I want us to advance together.
From what I see,
not many were after this just now.
But I think Keun Woo is going to get
Area A.
If Keun Woo were to go backward,
we would need this area for sure.
This area is going to explode.
Let's keep this safe...
and go in here. That's for the best.
Are you worried he'd outrun you?
- You are, right?
- Yes.
But Seung Yong has a booster.
He could use it.
Seung Yong has a Zero.
Oh, right. Lucky me.
Then Ji Hoo will try to outrun me.
Will YunB let that happen?
Since he has to advance as well?
In my opinion,
- Among them.
- YunB would feel safe in the back.
YunB is probably in the middle-low rank.
- Right?
- YunB could join...
just because there's a gap.
Seung Yong and Ji Hoo
are in the top ranks,
and YunB can join only because
he's in the lower ranks.
- He might overlap with us.
- Exactly.
- If YunB is helping out the others,
- Interesting.
we could buy this one.
True.
(The strategy is to keep YunB,
the first player, in check.)
Heo Seong Beom, here's your green card.
Thank you.
(Heo Seong Beom bets a 5 on Area C.)
You've placed Card Five in Area C.
(Choi Hye Seon bets on Area D.)
Place your card
in the area of your choice.
(Hong Jin Ho bets on Area B.)
I think this is a crucial turning point.
It's a golden opportunity to tie...
Jin Ho down.
Since Keun Woo goes later,
Jin Ho is guaranteed to get tied down.
(Jeong Keun Woo, Hong Jin Ho)
The best option we have is...
to win the most bets.
If YunB wins Area C and I win Area A,
I could drag Hye Seon...
or Seong Beom down.
It'd be amazing if you could win either...
Area B or Area D.
Okay.
(The strategy is to keep Jin Ho in check.)
Hi.
You've placed Card Four in Area A.
(YunB bets on Area C.)
(Ji Hoo bets on Area B.)
All players have placed their bets.
(Round 11 Betting Results)
(A: Shin Seung Yong,
B: Hong Jin Ho, Kang Ji Hoo)
(C: Heo Seong Beom, YunB,
D: Choi Hye Seon)
I will announce the betting results.
Area A goes to Hyun Sung Joo.
How did he do that?
Area B goes to Kang Ji Hoo.
Area C goes to Heo Seong Beom.
Area D goes to Jeong Keun Woo.
- Keun Woo didn't get the reverse.
- No, he didn't.
Keun Woo doesn't have to move.
Are you sure?
Isn't there a plan we don't know about?
Should we let Sunny go?
Sunny
- The numbers are 3 and 4, right?
- Yes.
Hye Seon, do you want to take
the outer course or the inner course?
The inner course looks risky.
I'll take the outer one.
Let's go all out.
Okay.
Hyun Sung Joo, please place your cards.
Is our burger finally going to move?
Let me go backward, Sung Joo.
Please help Three go backward.
Help Shin Seung Yong go backward.
Are you asking your car
to be flipped over?
I've already made up my mind.
- Good one.
- Nice. He's helping us out.
(Sung Joo gets rid of
the two stacked-up cars.)
Sung Joo must want to get rid of it fast.
Jeong Keun Woo, please place your cards.
(It's betting ace Keun Woo's turn.)
I wonder if you have Card One left.
How about placing Zero on mine?
(Kang Ji Hoo: 3)
You're giving Three to me?
Do you have Card One left?
Zero to Shin Seung Yong.
(Heo Seong Beom: 2, 1)
Thank you, Keun Woo.
Zero...
- You want it?
- Please.
Will you be moving forward with Zero?
- Zero...
- No, I'd stay still.
This would disappear,
which would be favorable for Seung Yong.
I see. Are you desperate, Seung Yong?
- Please. Help me.
- I'm discarding it.
I'm discarding it.
His plea has been discarded.
Kang Ji Hoo, please place your cards.
(Kang Ji Hoo)
(Shin Seung Yong)
Doesn't this look right?
- It's not bad.
- What about this one?
- Discard it.
- Give it to someone.
I kind of want to help someone.
- Discard it.
- Should I?
If I place it here,
you could move to the left.
Okay, I'm going with this.
(Kang Ji Hoo, Shin Seung Yong)
Ji Hoo is making a move.
Ji Hoo, girlfriend?
(Round 11)
(Everyone can move
besides YunB and Hyun Sung Joo.)
The race cars will start moving now.
Heo Seong Beom, booster activated.
You will start two spaces ahead.
My plan wasn't to move this fast.
One space forward and one space left.
Look at him making a comeback from behind.
What a weird world.
- I was here.
- Exactly.
- It's just like life.
- Unbelievable.
It won't work out for me.
Hong Jin Ho, you cannot move.
What is this, long-term parking?
- The parking fee is beyond imagination.
- Is this Incheon International Airport?
Choi Hye Seon,
3 spaces forward and 1 space right.
Yes!
How's the view from over there, Hye Seon?
- You can see the finish line from there.
- It's great.
- The finish line is visible, right?
- Right?
How's the view?
Shin Seung Yong, booster activated.
You will start two spaces ahead.
One space right.
- Gosh.
- You've collided with the wall.
Your race car has flipped over,
and you cannot move until the next round.
Come on. Why didn't you save me?
Jeong Keun Woo, two spaces backward.
It was hard getting there,
but I'm back to where I was before.
Kang Ji Hoo, three spaces forward.
(Kang Ji Hoo: Predicted 2nd)
He's turning with Hye Seon.
- Congratulations.
- The youngsters are fast.
All players have completed their moves.
(Round 11 Movement Results)
(Player, predicted rank:)
(1. Choi Hye Seon, 2. Kang Ji Hoo,
3. Heo Seong Beom, 4. Shin Seung Yong,)
(5. YunB, 6. Hong Jin Ho,
7. Hyun Sung Joo, 8. Jeong Keun Woo)
Can you wake me up when you move your car?
I think...
Hye Seon is indeed first
in the predicted rank.
She's in the top ranks.
Their plan is to make it possible
to end the game...
whenever possible.
Round 12 will begin now.
(Round 12, Seong Beom)
We're first in the upcoming turn
and the next one.
I'm in a good position to pull ahead.
(Team P3 Alliance
goes 1st twice in a row.)
(Heo Seong Beom,
Hong Jin Ho, Choi Hye Seon)
I'm thinking of betting with 3 and 3...
- I see.
- or 4 and 2.
- If we bet 4 and 2...
- It overlaps with 3 and 3.
Right? But Three does move first.
- You're right.
- It does.
Seung Yong from the other team can't move.
But Ji Hoo can move.
Even YunB...
can't move
because of the One on the right.
Only Ji Hoo can move.
But even if he does move,
Ji Hoo can't attack us.
I doubt everyone will choose both areas.
I'm going to discard the card this time.
Where will you discard it to?
Area B.
Then I'll discard it...
in Area A.
- You?
- Yes.
Got it.
(As Jin Ho predicted,
Ji Hoo and Seung Yong bet with low cards.)
Right now...
The best case is...
If I were to win Area D and place Three,
I'll be in front of you,
and you'll get the booster.
Right.
(YunB makes a safe bet on Area D.)
You just want to stay there, don't you?
- No.
- No? Do you want to move?
- Of course.
- Is that so?
Why wouldn't I move when I've got a car?
I felt pretty guilty.
I have to go slow.
(Keun Woo bets on Area D.)
(Sung Joo also bets on Area D.)
What I can't decide on is how much to bet.
I think it's best to secure good cards...
when we're the first to play.
Using Five seems like a good idea.
We deliberately set up
three consecutive turns...
because we wanted to make big bets
when we had the first move...
and win the big cards.
We could use the cards we wanted...
and block the other teams
from playing whatever they've planned.
Ta-da.
Choi Hye Seon.
You've placed Card Five in Area A.
Hong Jin Ho.
You've placed Card Four in Area C.
Why did you only use Card One?
This is a throwaway round.
What?
The later rounds are more important,
and Team P3 Alliance's turn
is about to start.
We don't have any aggressive moves to make
at the moment.
I don't think...
it's a good idea
to just throw it away whole.
Only one player should make the sacrifice.
If the other team wins all three,
we can't catch up to them anymore.
All players have placed their bets.
(Round 12: Betting Ends)
I will announce the betting results.
(Round 12 Betting Results)
(A: Choi Hye Seon, Kang Ji Hoo,
B: Shin Seung Yong, C: Hong Jin Ho,)
(D: YunB, Jeong Keun Woo, Hyun Sung Joo)
Area A goes to Choi Hye Seon.
Good for you.
Area B...
goes to Shin Seung Yong.
What about me?
(Team P3 Alliance
focused on Areas A and C.)
How about we...
We need to go with Plan B.
(A backup bet in Area A
that was considered more important)
You've placed Card Two in Area A.
(Thanks to it,
Seung Yong won Area B with Card 1.)
Thank you.
Area C goes to Hong Jin Ho.
Area D...
- goes to Jeong Keun Woo.
- What?
Seriously?
Isn't this scripted?
Are you sure this isn't scripted?
How did things turn out like this?
He's a genius.
I'm now tired of hearing
that I won an area.
And I knew I'd win it.
I interacted with Keun Woo
a handful of times.
He should go to Kangwon Land.
- Goodness, you...
- This is wild.
- Gosh.
- How is this possible?
Keun Woo has the highest winning rate.
(YunB fails every bet he's in
against Keun Woo.)
Seong Beom should get...
(Heo Seong Beom: 2)
One first.
- I'm going to crush him.
- From over there...
- Get on top of mine.
- Ji Hoo can't move.
This feels right for Ji Hoo.
Like so.
Is it better to go right or left?
- Right.
- Weren't you taking the inside line?
Why left when he's already Two?
- Do you want to flip over?
- Right.
Flipping over seems riskier.
(Hong Jin Ho: 4)
Choi Hye Seon, please place your cards.
Give me Three.
(Hong Jin Ho: 3, 4)
(Heo Seong Beom: 2, 1)
- Who needs Three?
- Sung Joo.
Would you like it?
Sung Joo wants it.
He won't say it with confidence.
All he's doing is nodding.
Or should I move farther?
No. They'll probably use reverse.
- Right.
- No, that's bad.
Do you need it, Sung Joo?
Do as you'd like.
- He doesn't need it.
- Choi Hye Seon has discarded a card.
Should I save your Zero?
That'd be great.
You should give YunB 2 and me 1.
It's the same for me either way
because Seong Beom will crush me.
(His car will be crushed by Seong Beom's.)
(Choi Hye Seon: Reverse)
- Two. Like this?
- Yes.
(Kang Ji Hoo: 1)
Hye Seon's car is going to go backward.
I expected it. It's not even a surprise.
- They're really coming after her.
- Jeong Keun Woo,
please place your cards.
- Where...
- Let's see.
(Jeong Keun Woo: 1, 2)
- Jeong Keun Woo has discarded a card.
- He's a tough man.
He's a real tough man.
(Round 12)
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
and Jin Ho can move.)
I think Keun Woo is in last place.
That's my guess.
Right? There's no reason
why he wouldn't use three.
Seeing how he didn't use just three...
The race cars will start moving now.
Seong Beom, one space forward...
and one space left.
(Heo Seong Beom)
You've collided with Ji Hoo's race car.
Crash.
Sorry, Ji Hoo.
(Round 12)
Jin Ho, three spaces forward...
and one space right.
Gosh, he's going far.
Get ready to collide.
Three layers for three people.
I'm the head.
Keun Woo, one space forward...
and one space right.
Ji Hoo, you cannot move.
YunB, booster activated.
You will start two spaces ahead.
One space forward and one space left.
They're going together.
- There you go.
- He's right behind me.
Seung Yong, your car can move now.
Yes!
(Round 12 Movement Results)
(Player, predicted rank:
1. Choi Hye Seon, 2. Heo Seong Beom,)
(3. Kang Ji Hoo, 4. YunB,
5. Hong Jin Ho, 6. Shin Seung Yong,)
(7. Hyun Sung Joo, 8. Jeong Keun Woo)
Round 13 will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Round 13, Jin Ho)
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,)
(Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
Others will reverse other than me
in this round.
Two will reverse.
(Choi Hye Seon, Reverse)
(Heading straight to the Voting Room)
Keun Woo.
Place your card
in the area of your choice.
You've placed Card Three in Area D.
- You're done already?
- Yes.
We're all being dragged by him.
He's taking everything.
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
Area A goes to Hong Jin Ho.
(Area A goes to Hong Jin Ho.)
Area B goes to Kang Ji Hoo.
(Area B goes to Kang Ji Hoo.)
Area C goes to Shin Seung Yong.
(Area C goes to Shin Seung Yong.)
Area D goes to Jeong Keun Woo.
Stop letting me take the areas.
You guys... Aren't you going to keep up?
- Hey.
- Gosh, I placed my bet too.
You guys are funny.
(YunB lost the area to Keun Woo
five times already.)
(Round 12 Betting Results)
(A: Hong Jin Ho, Hyun Sung Joo,
B: Kang Ji Hoo, Heo Seong Beom)
(C: Shin Seung Yong, D: Jeong Keun Woo,
YunB, Choi Hye Seon)
You will now place your movement cards.
(Placing movement cards)
Hong Jin Ho, please place your cards.
(Round 13, Jin Ho, Seung Yong,
Keun Woo, Ji Hoo)
(Hong Jin Ho)
(Round 13, Jin Ho, Seung Yong,
Keun Woo, Ji Hoo)
Seung Yong, I helped you.
You want my car to flip over again?
No, I helped you to go far.
You're so mean.
- Darn.
- Shin Seung Yong,
please place your cards.
(Round 13, Jin Ho, Seung Yong,
Keun Woo, Ji Hoo)
(Sighing)
How will you use the reverse card?
I think you can use it on Seong Beom.
Right.
Stop sending me back!
That team got the reverse card well,
but they couldn't get the hang of it.
Why do they keep using
the reverse card on us?
After everything I went through
to get here.
I made it to second place
after going through a lot.
You have ten seconds left.
If I use it...
I'll use the reverse card on him.
I'll use either 3 or 4 on him.
Hurry, you're running out of time.
No, there.
(Round 13, Jin Ho, Seung Yong,
Keun Woo, Ji Hoo)
(Seong Beom, reverse)
Where should I use zero?
Your time is up.
The card will be discarded.
- Gosh, darn it.
- Let's see.
(Round 13, Jin Ho, Seung Yong,
Keun Woo, Ji Hoo)
Jeong Keun Woo, please place your cards.
(Round 13, Jin Ho, Seung Yong,
Keun Woo, Ji Hoo)
(Keun Woo, 2, 3)
(Hye Seon, 1)
(He's done placing his cards.)
(Keun Woo gave the lowest card, 1,
to Hye Seon.)
Thank you, Keun Woo.
- Why does he keep helping?
- Thank you.
I'm the most curious...
about the rank Keun Woo
predicted himself to win.
I know.
(Predicted 7th, currently 7th)
All the movement cards have been placed.
The race cars will start moving now.
Hong Jin Ho, one space forward...
and one space left.
Choi Hye Seon,
one space backward.
Shin Seung Yong, two spaces forward...
and two spaces left.
You've collided with YunB's race car.
They collided.
(Seung Yong and YunB's cars collided.)
Jeong Keun Woo, two spaces forward...
and one space right.
(Jeong Keun Woo is maintaining 7th place
that he predicted.)
Heo Seong Beom, three spaces backward.
(Heo Seong Beom, currently 6th place)
(Heo Seong Beom places 6th,
the rank he predicted.)
Do something about that.
(Heo Seong Beom places 6th,
the rank he predicted.)
All players have completed their moves.
(Round 13 Movement Results)
(Hye Seon, Jin Ho, Ji Hoo, Seung Yong,
YunB, Seong Beom, Keun Woo, Sung Joo)
Round 14 will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(A: Shin Seung Yong, Hyun Sung Joo,
Jeong Keun Woo)
(B: Heo Seong Beom, Hong Jin Ho, C: YunB)
(D: Choi Hye Seon, Kang Ji Hoo)
All the movement cards have been placed.
(Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Hye Seon, and Seung Yong can move.)
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
The race cars will start moving now.
Choi Hye Seon, two spaces forward,
one space right.
Racer Choi Hye Seon is going forward.
Yes!
Shin Seung Yong, one space forward.
Kang Ji Hoo, one space forward.
YunB, booster activated.
You will start two spaces ahead.
YunB, three spaces forward.
(YunB, currently 2nd place)
(YunB is closer to 3rd place,
the rank he predicted.)
Heo Seong Beom, two spaces right.
(Heo Seong Beom and Jeong Keun Woo
managed to maintain their predicted rank.)
All players have completed their moves.
(Round 14 Movement Results)
(Choi Hye Seon, YunB, Kang Ji Hoo,
Shin Seung Yong, Hong Jin Ho,)
(Heo Seong Beom, Jeong Keun Woo,
Hyun Sung Joo)
Round 15 will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Round 15, Sung Joo)
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Jin Ho,
Hye Seon, Jung Joo, Seung Yong)
- What is 1-1-1?
- It's 1-1-1?
- Hye Seon is last, right?
- Yes.
I think Hye Seon is in last place...
or in bottom places,
but they'll make her win first place.
I think Jin Ho and Seong Beom...
predicted to be 2nd and 3rd place.
Seong Beom seems really anxious.
I think so.
So let's focus on getting
on Seong Beom's way.
It'll be better
to send away Jin Ho quietly.
What ranks did they predict to be in?
- What?
- YunB's must not be so low.
- Right.
- He...
It was so obvious YunB
wanted to finish the race.
- Was it?
- Yes.
We can't be at ease until the end.
If Ji Hoo predicted to be in first place,
he'd have wanted to finish the race first.
Right. Ji Hoo seemed...
eager to finish the race.
- Right? In the beginning.
- Yes.
So when Keun Woo gave him
four spaces backward,
- he was really disappointed.
- Yes.
I thought that was a real reaction.
So I thought he predicted
to be in the top ranks.
Me too. I think
it's either 1st or 2nd place.
- First or second?
- Yes.
First or second?
I bet Ji Hoo predicted
to be in first place.
He probably wanted to win first place,
at least through this.
At first, I thought Ji Hoo wouldn't...
predict to be 2nd or 1st place...
because he knows the risk.
But seeing
how he couldn't hide his feelings,
I thought YunB and he...
predicted to be in 2nd and 3rd place.
But YunB formed alliance with them...
after submitting his predicted rank.
So I even thought their ranks...
could overlap.
Did the both of them write second place?
If that's not the case,
it could be them finishing the race
2nd and 3rd.
Did you predict to be in last place?
- What?
- Did you predict to be in last place?
I can't tell you.
Please just go this time.
- What?
- Just go this time.
Me? I can't go by myself.
You should use the cards on me
for me to go.
How did you end up like this?
- What?
- How did you end up like this?
You get abandoned if you play alone.
Why did you choose to be abandoned?
- What?
- Why did you choose to be abandoned?
The choice of words is important.
It means...
he chose to go solo.
I made a choice before I was abandoned.
- That looks cooler.
- Me?
I'm suddenly getting so sad.
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
- Let's see.
- Area A...
- Who took it?
- has no winners.
- It's gone.
- This is good.
Area B goes to Hong Jin Ho.
Area C goes to Kang Ji Hoo.
Area D goes to Heo Seong Beom.
(Round 15 Betting Results)
(B: Hong Jin Ho, C: Kang Ji Hoo,
D: Heo Seong Beom)
You will now place your movement cards.
Kang Ji Hoo, please place your cards.
(Attacking Seong Beom
with 4 spaces backward)
- Is it reverse?
- Yes. Four spaces backward?
- Gosh.
- What was that?
That was a major attack.
What? Why does he keep
taking Seong Beom down?
Because he's on the opposite team.
- But he...
- He must have a plan.
He must have a reason.
(Round 15, Ji Hoo, Seong Beom, Jin Ho)
Two...
Seong Beom was attacked...
and that
I think that was a waste of cards.
They didn't know the rank
Seong Beom predicted to be in,
so they attacked him like that.
But we knew Seong Beom
predicted to be in sixth place,
so it was better for us.
We were actually thankful.
The race cars will start moving now.
(Ji Hoo, Seong Beom, Jin Ho,
and Hye Seon can move.)
Kang Ji Hoo, two spaces right.
Heo Seong Beom, four spaces backward.
No!
Round and round,
and I'm right back where I started.
Okay, I did enough.
Seong Beom can't make it back.
I don't have to mess with him anymore.
Hong Jin Ho, two spaces forward...
and one space right.
Vroom.
I'm in the same position as YunB.
You're here.
Finally.
I predicted...
to end in first place.
- First of all...
- I think...
(During the preliminary meting)
I was going for the top rank.
No matter what?
If I want to win first place,
I just need to go forward.
So I don't have to...
worry about anything else...
and go forward.
I think that'll work.
- I think 1st, 3rd, and 5th isn't so bad.
- Right. It's not bad.
Then I'll assist you guys.
- I'll go with this.
- Yes, that sounds good.
Jin Ho,
choose your predicted rank.
you predicted you would be in first place.
Instead of predicting
to finish in top ranks,
predicting to be in lower ranks...
and going forward while being wary...
is an easier way.
That way, you can be flexible too.
That's what I think,
but when I first started the game,
I just wanted to win first place,
no matter what.
I just...
got that feeling.
So I thought I wanted to
win first place today.
That's the feeling I got.
I'd win first place,
Hye Seon 3rd place,
and Seong Beom 6th place.
That's the plan we started with.
Hong Jin Ho, two spaces forward,
one space right.
(Jin Ho made it to 2nd place.)
Vroom.
I didn't have a feeling that I'd lose.
Jin Ho surged into the lead.
So I thought...
he predicted to be
in 1st, 2nd, or 3rd place.
Choi Hye Seon, one space forward.
All players have completed their moves.
(Round 15 Movement Results)
(Choi Hye Seon, Hong Jin Ho, YunB,
Kang Ji Hoo, Shin Seung Yong...)
Round 16 will begin now.
After Round 15,
I tried to focus a lot...
to make my win happen.
We had to do our best...
in the remaining rounds...
to create the best possible situation
for us...
even if we can't come out on top.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
Let's go.
(Round 16, Seung Yong)
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
Jin Ho, Hye Seon, Sung Joo, Seung Yong)
Ji Hoo, come here.
Area C would be the worst for you.
If they give you zero for left,
you'll collide for sure.
(Kang Ji Hoo)
(Ji Hoo's race car will flip over
if he goes to the right.)
I think one of us should finish the race
with high numbers.
To make it completely safe. Right?
We don't have to take reverse.
We're going later anyway,
so we won't be able to place reverse.
Let's give up Area B this time.
- Discard Area B.
- Right.
(They give up betting on
Area B and Area D.)
I think we don't have to
push so hard in this round.
If they...
are after Hye Seon,
they'd have taken 3 and 3 or 3 and 4.
They'll take Area B,
or Area C and Area B...
or Area C and Area D.
We should try to take Area A.
We should go after Area A and Area C.
- Where should we bet?
- Let's discuss that.
We can discard Area D.
Actually, it'd be best for us...
if we pretend to be caught by them
and you getting caught by YunB.
I think we should go...
for Area A and Area C.
So if we take Area C,
let's give four to Seong Beom...
and make him go forward to the left.
I'll bet four on Area A,
and you should bet one...
as a backup plan.
We're using four too fast.
Is that so?
Then I'll bet three on Area A,
and you bet one as a backup plan.
- We could overlap.
- Okay.
Please refill.
- Jin Ho, here are the blue cards.
- Right, thank you.
Place your card
in the area of your choice.
Hong Jin Ho.
You've placed Card Three in Area A.
Heo Seong Beom.
You've placed Card One in Area A.
I need to give it my energy.
Choi Hye Seon.
You've placed Card Four in Area C.
- Is that right?
- It is.
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
- Area A.
- Let's see.
Area A goes to...
Hong Jin Ho.
- Congratulations.
- That's double two.
Area B goes to...
- Shin Seung Yong.
- Yes!
Not congratulating you.
Area C goes to...
- Choi Hye Seon.
- Yes!
Area D goes to...
Kang Ji Hoo.
- You took 1-3-3, right?
- Yes.
Shin Seung Yong, please place your cards.
What shall we do?
Wouldn't it be the best...
- if you use 1 and 3 on me?
- Oh, okay.
(Kang Ji Hoo)
(He places 3 and 1 in Ji Hoo's slots.)
(He places the rest in YunB's slot.)
Three and one?
(Kang Ji Hoo, Hong Jin Ho)
Are you going to catch me?
- Seong Beom.
- Yes?
- I think you got caught by Ji Hoo.
- What?
Hold on.
- I think you're right.
- Right?
If he goes one space forward...
and goes here, it'll be over.
One space forward...
One, two. You're right.
My strategy worked,
so I felt really proud.
If you give me 1 and 3,
I can catch Jin Ho.
That'd be the best option,
so I think we should take...
at least one area with 1 and 3.
I should?
It doesn't matter.
One of us will do.
It'll be best if you win it.
Then I'll bet five...
- on Area B first.
- Okay.
Think of how you can win
Area C and Area D,
- then place your bet.
- Okay.
They'll end with Seong Beom
in the next round.
So, Hye Seon and Jin Ho's turns are over.
They're done with their turns.
So we're at an advantage.
What I'm worried about is this.
We shouldn't use all the good cards
we have here.
I'll use mine, and you two...
- should save 4 and 5.
- Yes.
- I can give them to you.
- Right.
- You can use yours on me next.
- Okay.
(They discussed their strategy,
considering next round's turns.)
Here you are.
Shin Seung Yong.
You've placed Card Five in Area B.
(Shin Seung Yong placed 5 in Area B.)
Kang Ji Hoo.
You've placed Card Two in Area D.
It was lucky for us
to win the areas we bet on.
So, we could devise our strategy
for this round.
I couldn't think of me getting caught.
The situation wasn't great for us.
I thought, "How should we play
to overcome this?"
I kept thinking about that.
Kang Ji Hoo, please place your cards.
I can give them reverse and three.
But who...
Hold on.
No.
Should I give three to Sung Joo?
- Or...
- Should I give three to Sung Joo...
and reverse to Jin Ho?
Not bad.
(Hyung Sung Joo, Shin Seung Yong)
(Hong Jin Ho, reverse)
Hong Jin Ho, please place your cards.
It's my turn already?
(Jin Ho's cards of Area A: 2, 2, 1)
You have reverse.
You have to get rid of it.
Of course I will.
I'm thinking of where to place the rest.
Seung Yong is out there,
and he's over there.
If they didn't catch me...
Let's move Hye Seon.
Did I get too excited?
Okay.
- We could do that.
- That could work. Okay.
Okay.
I will...
remove that.
- This is Seong Beom.
- Two?
Okay.
(Choi Hye Seon)
Choi Hye Seon, please place your cards.
(Hye Seon's cards of Area C: 4, 0, 2)
(Heo Seong Beom, Shin Seung Yong)
(Remaining Movement Card, 2)
Should I discard it?
- Let's discard it.
Discard it if it's useless.
- Hye Seon has discarded a card.
- I couldn't think of that.
All the movement cards have been placed.
The race cars will start moving now.
(Everyone's cars except for
Keun Woo and YunB's cars can move.)
Seung Yong, one space forward.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo: 3 and 1,
YunB: 3 and R, Seong Beom: 4 and 0)
(Jin Ho: 1 and Reverse, Hye Seon: 2 and 2,
Sung Joo: 3 and 4, Seung Yong)
Taking the inside line is a lot faster.
Taking the inside line is important.
Ji Hoo, 1 space forward and 2 spaces left.
(Ji Hoo's car
goes on top of Jin Ho's car.)
You're too heavy.
- Get off me.
- Gosh.
You've collided with Jin Ho's race car.
Why come all the way here?
Seong Beom, four spaces left.
(Keun Woo, Ji Hoo: 3 and 1,
YunB: 3 and R, Seong Beom)
(Jin Ho: 1 and Reverse, Hye Seon: 2 and 2,
Sung Joo: 3 and 4, Seung Yong)
Jin Ho, you cannot move.
Okay.
(He can't move as Ji Hoo's car
is on top of his.)
Hye Seon, two spaces forward.
Yes!
Please move Sung Joo's car quickly.
- He gets to move after three hours.
- Is he finally moving?
I thought his tires went out.
The insanely slow starter.
Sung Joo, 3 spaces forward
and 1 space right.
So his car does have tires.
(Round 16 Movement Results)
All players have completed their moves.
Round 17 will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Keun Woo)
The numbers 4, 0, and 2 keep popping up.
Most of the players
will be focused on their team's...
or alliance's movement.
I would've been out of their interest.
I was satisfied with that.
And overall,
if I started the game with around
a win rate of 20 to 30 percent,
I believe I'm at 30 to 40 percent now.
I liked being at the back,
but I couldn't place last.
So I did feel a bit anxious.
I have to stop acting...
and start pacing forward.
Sung Joo, place your card
in the area of your choice.
A drastic number isn't good for me.
I wanted a number
that could move me gently...
by 1 space left or 1 space forward.
Sung Joo,
you've placed Card Two in Area A.
Right.
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
Area A goes to Sung Joo.
Gosh.
Area B goes to Hye Seon.
Area C goes to YunB.
Area D has no winners.
You will now place your movement cards.
YunB, please place your cards.
(YunB's cards of Area C: 1, Reverse, 3)
Seong Beom will reverse three spaces.
After that,
you should use one...
or give it to me.
It's one or the other.
(Round 17, YunB, Hye Seon, Sung Joo)
(Jin Ho: 3, Reverse)
- I'll take one.
- Okay.
(YunB: 3, 1)
I think we can accurately predict
2nd and 3rd place.
- We can do that.
- Right.
Hye Seon, please place your cards.
(Hye Seon's cards of Area B: 4, 0, 2)
- Answer me with a voice filled with rage.
- Right.
Should we flip Ji Hoo's car over for now?
That's a good idea.
Right. That's the only move possible.
What should we do? Is that better?
- That's...
- That's the best move, right?
Right. That's the best move.
Let's flip Ji Hoo's car.
Let's flip it over.
Should I place it on yours?
One space to the right?
- My car? YunB will go there.
- Doesn't that work?
Move it to the left.
- The left of your car?
- Right.
(Hong Jin Ho: 2)
Sung Joo, please place your cards.
(Sung Joo's cards of Area A: 2, 3, 1)
(He places the cards on his gear board.)
(The movement card left is 3.)
Will you give that to us?
If you're torn, place it next to two.
Let's destroy it all.
Destroy it all!
Sung Joo has discarded a card.
All the movement cards have been placed.
The race cars will start moving now.
(Ji Hoo, YunB, Seong Beom,
and Sung Joo's cars can move.)
Ji Hoo, four spaces right.
You've collided with the wall.
Your race car has flipped over,
and you cannot move until the next round.
Okay.
YunB, 1 space forward and 2 spaces left.
Seong Beom, three spaces backward.
No!
(Seong Beom: 3, Reverse)
You've placed last for the first time
in your life, right?
Yes.
- What a jerk.
- Think that you're first from behind.
I'm first from behind.
Sung Joo, 1 space forward
and 1 space left.
Let's go past halfway.
(Round 17 Movement Results)
(Player, predicted rank)
All players have completed their moves.
(Hye Seon 3, YunB 3, Ji Hoo 2, Jin Ho 1,)
(Seung Yong 7, Sung Joo 7,
Keun Woo 7, Seong Beom 6)
Round 18 will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(Ji Hoo)
(Keun Woo only goes forward.)
Keun Woo, place your card
in the area of your choice.
Keun Woo,
you've placed your card in Area B.
Is that right?
Yes.
Seong Beom had to move forward.
I had to move in slightly to the inside...
to raise the chance
of me placing seventh...
even though it may end up as a tie.
For me to take the inside line,
I had to get that area no matter what.
This time,
it will be good for you to take Area A.
Because I go first?
(Ji Hoo's remaining cards)
Ji Hoo, you've placed Card Five in Area A.
There was a reason why I played five.
I saved 5 and 4
as they were the best cards.
I thought that many other players would
play their fives after saving them up.
Playing 5 now and saving 4...
for the last round
seemed like a better play.
That was why I did that.
The most important rounds for us
are the last round...
and Round 19.
Rounds 17 and 18 are also important,
but keeping my position...
wasn't a bad option.
Seung Yong,
you've placed Card Two in Area B.
YunB, you've placed Card One in Area D.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
It's the best for us to get Area C.
If we do that,
Seong Beom can go to Sung Joo
with 3 or 4 and stop him.
Right.
- Let's do that.
- Right.
The game is slowly reaching the end.
Hye Seon,
(Hye Seon's remaining cards)
place your card
in the area of your choice.
Okay.
Hye Seon,
you've placed Card Three in Area A.
Seong Beom,
you've placed Card Two in Area C.
(Jin Ho's remaining cards)
(Team P3 Alliance placed 2 card
in Area C.)
Jin Ho, you've placed Card Five in Area C.
All players have placed their bets.
Will we win it this time?
I will announce the betting results.
Area A.
(Ji Hoo and Hye Seon
made a bet for Area A.)
(Sung Joo's remaining cards)
Sung Joo, place your card
in the area of your choice.
(Sung Joo's remaining cards)
Sung Joo,
you've placed Card Three in Area.
Area A goes to Ji Hoo.
(Area A goes to Ji Hoo.)
Area B goes to Keun Woo.
(Area B goes to Keun Woo.)
- Area C goes to Jin Ho.
- Right.
Area D goes to YunB.
(Area D goes to YunB.)
- We got it by fluke.
- What?
We got it by fluke.
You will now place your movement cards.
Ji Hoo, please place your cards.
I checked to see who I should pull back.
Jin Ho kept pacing forward.
I thought that he was betting for
1st, 2nd, or 3rd.
"I can't stand and watch."
(Ji Hoo places reverse on Jin Ho.)
Where must I place the other two?
What do you have?
We can play up to five...
- since our turns are next to each other.
- Right.
I think we can discard them.
- Discard them?
- Let's not discard them.
I'll give Seung Yong 1
and place 1 on mine.
If two is placed,
my car won't crash.
That will happen...
- if I place two.
- Right.
- Right?
- Yes.
(YunB places 2 on the left
of his gear board.)
YunB, please place your card.
(He places 3 on the right
of his gear board.)
I'll place one on Keun Woo's board.
But if you do that,
aren't we helping them...
by letting them use it
whenever they want to?
- How about we discard both of them?
- All right.
YunB has discarded the cards.
Jin Ho, please place your cards.
Right.
After that,
let's see. I'll give one to you, Hye Seon.
- I think it'll be better to do that.
- Right.
- Place one on hers.
- Place it on hers.
- It's best to be at the front.
- It's the left, right?
- Yes.
Double check.
(He places 2 on Hye Seon's left.)
Keun Woo, please place your cards.
His straightforwardness.
Am I right?
I'm right.
(Keun Woo places 3 and 0
on his gear board as planned.)
What place did you bet for?
You wanted to go back so much earlier.
Keun Woo is...
He's controlling the game.
(The controller of this game, Keun Woo)
All right. Go, Seung Yong.
All the movement cards have been placed.
The race cars will start moving now.
(Keung Woo: 3, 0, Ji Hoo: Unknown,
YunB: 2, 3, Seong Beom: 3, 4,)
(Jin Ho: 2, Reverse, Hye Seon: 2, R,
Sung Joo, Seung Yong: 1, 1)
YunB, 2 spaces forward and 1 space right.
What? Did things get turned around?
Seong Beom, 3 spaces forward
and 1 space right.
You've collided with Sung Joo's race car.
(Seong Beom's car went on top
of Sung Joo's car.)
Jin Ho, two spaces backward.
(Jin Ho, moves two spaces backward.)
"It's a really tough game
to take first place."
"Did I come up with the wrong plan?"
It was a moment
that made me feel those things.
Seung Yong, one space forward.
(Seung Yong, moves one space forward.)
Keun Woo, three spaces left.
(Keun Woo, moves three spaces left.)
I got it done. I entered a safe course.
"There's no one who can stop me."
Why is that?
The ones who picked the top places,
won't be looking at me.
They have to look forward.
All the movement cards have been placed.
(All the movement cards have been placed
for Round 18.)
(Round 18 Movement Results)
(Player, predicted rank)
(YunB 3, Hye Seon 3, Ji Hoo 2,)
(Seung Yong unknown, Jin Ho 1, Keun Woo 7,
Seong Beom 6, Sung Joo unknown)
Round 19 will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(YunB)
I must do well here.
This is fun. It's hard to predict
how things will go until the end.
There are two rounds left.
There are three in our team,
and the cards we can get are limited.
It's going to be about
who we will push for the lead.
Even if we want to push Jin Ho,
he's in a position
that isn't that threatening.
- You're in a dangerous spot.
- Right.
This was my first time playing this game.
I wondered what the best way was
to play this game.
Until the middle of the game,
we could've all made aggressive plays...
by attacking, defending,
and smashing the others.
That was a bit disappointing
now that I think about it.
Would you like to join us?
It's the end of the game.
There are two rounds left.
- I'll pick my cards first.
- Okay.
(Keun Woo decides to join Team P3 Alliance
for the remaining rounds.)
I was in 3rd place in Round 19.
I was near the wall on the right.
It was so easy for the Alliance...
to make my car crash to the right.
I have no hope
if my car flips over at this point.
I won't be able to move during Round 20.
I'll end the game in third place.
(Keun Woo's remaining cards)
Keun Woo,
you've placed Card Three in Area D.
(Keun Woo places Card 3 in Area D.)
But...
if they get any card,
they can flip over my car.
YunB has to get it first to save me.
- Right now,
- Yes?
this is my last time I get to go first.
You're next.
(YunB is the 1st player in Round 19.)
Are you guys almost there?
We're in a pretty good spot.
I can tell you that much.
What places did you guys bet for?
- What?
- What places did you guys bet for?
- Do you want to know?
- Yes.
I'll pretend not to know.
All right. Make sure to keep our deal.
Ji Hoo has to place second.
(YunB tells Sung Joo the predicted ranks
of his alliance.)
- Ji Hoo?
- Second.
- Second? And?
- Yes.
- I have to place third.
- Right. And?
Sung Joo and I were both in Team P2.
He suggested that we form an alliance.
I was someone he could trust,
and we had a connection through Team P2.
When he suggested that
we form an alliance toward the end,
we checked each other's predicted ranks.
You two should go outside and talk.
(YunB makes Sung Joo
and Seung Yong talk with each other.)
Do you need Area C right now?
- Me?
- Yes.
It doesn't matter for us.
What do you need?
I think I definitely need Area C.
- Area C?
- Yes.
What place do you have to be in?
- Is it the same rank as mine?
- No.
- What's your predicted rank?
- It's around that.
You won't tell me? I told you.
(Sung Joo double-checks the rank
he heard from YunB.)
Tell me if we have the same rank.
It's fine as we don't have the same rank.
The reason I can't tell you...
is because it'll be the end of me
once people hear about it.
I haven't formed an alliance with anyone.
This is my first time
reaching out to your team.
I'm worried that the others might ask...
after we talk together.
- So you won't tell me?
- Anyway...
I wasn't able to...
fully trust Sung Joo.
- All right.
- Hold on.
My predicted rank is six.
It's hard to predict
what the others have under their sleeves.
There's no one who I can fully trust.
But in the intense moments
toward the end of the semi-finals,
I must give my trust.
There's no other choice.
Things started to flow again...
like the alliance game we were used to.
Then...
(Sung Joo and Seung Yong decide
to share their betting information.)
I think it'll be better for you
to place five for Area C.
Or it can be four.
We're planning to...
sweep away everything
during the next round.
Okay. I'll make my bet.
(It turns out to be a 4-on-4 match
toward the end.)
Jin Ho, place your card
in the area of your choice.
I'm broke.
(Jin Ho's remaining cards)
(Jin Ho places Card 4 in Area A.)
Jin Ho, you've placed Card Four in Area A.
I can't give up until the end.
I tried to get the best result
after placing my bet.
I was determined to
attack and defend well.
Seong Beom,
you've placed Card Five in Area C.
The other team is still using
the reverse card well.
I was even more determined...
to take away...
the reverse card from them.
(Hye Seon's remaining cards)
Hye Seon,
you've placed Card Two in Area B.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
(Hye Seon bets a 2 on Area B.)
Sung Joo, place your card
in the area of your choice.
(Sung Joo decides to make a bet
on Area C.)
Sung Joo, you've placed a card in Area C.
Right.
Seung Yong,
you've placed Card Three in Area C.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
(Seung Yong bets a 3 on Area C.)
YunB, you've placed a card in Area A.
Ji Hoo, place your card
in the area of your choice.
(Ji Hoo's remaining cards)
Ji Hoo, you've placed Card One in Area B.
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
Area A...
goes to Jin Ho.
Area B...
goes to Hye Seon.
Jin Ho and Hye Seon had the early turns,
but they won the areas.
It was a very dangerous situation.
Area C goes to Seung Yong.
Area D goes to Keun Woo.
(Round 19 Betting Results)
You will now place your movement cards.
Jin Ho, please place your cards.
Come over to me, Hye Seon and Seong Beom.
Hold on.
Which cards do you have, Hye Seon?
(Jin Ho and Hye Seon will place
6 cards consecutively.)
The moment 1 of these 2
push my car to the right,
I get eliminated from Bloody Game.
I felt so nervous...
at that moment.
But I had to pretend to be calm.
(He does his best to look calm
while eating the chocolate biscuit.)
That's hard to decide.
Let's move Seung Yong.
Let's see.
Three and four.
No. It has to move to the left.
- It's the right, right?
- Yes.
(Jin Ho's last card is placed
on Seong Beom's right.)
Hye Seon, please place your cards.
(She places 2 on Seong Beom's left.)
- Stop Sung Joo from going to the left.
- Right.
- It has to be placed here.
- Place that one...
on the right of Seung Yong.
Right.
(The remaining card gets placed
on Seung Yong's gear board.)
They didn't seem to know
my predicted rank.
They didn't flip my car.
Seung Yong, please place your cards.
I can get on top of Hye Seon's car.
(Ji Hoo's car can collide
with Hye Seon's car with 3 and 2.)
(Seung Yong places 3 and 2
on Ji Hoo's gear board.)
(Keun Woo is next after Seung Yong.)
What do you want to do?
Or you can move Seung Yong by one space.
Which cards do you have?
I was able to secure seventh place.
But Seong Beom came to me at that moment.
"Where are you going to go, Keun Woo?"
Hold on.
I turned my head,
and I saw the reverse card
on my gear board.
(The reverse card
was placed on Keun Woo's gear board.)
"I'm in trouble"
"Why didn't I catch that?"
"I was too careless."
Keun Woo, please place your cards.
This was something I felt
while playing the game.
Keun Woo...
kept playing the game
while looking like a solo player,
but he kept making plays...
to help the alliance of three.
(During Round 11)
Please!
(Keun Woo had the chance
to help Seung Yong.)
This disappears, so it helps Seung Yong.
Oh, this disappears?
Are you desperate, Seung Yong?
Please help me!
(He discarded the card
even after hearing his plea.)
There weren't many places...
for the reverse card,
so I placed it on Keun Woo's gear board...
and decided to help Ji Hoo.
All the movement cards have been placed.
The race cars will start moving now.
(Keun Woo: Reverse, Ji Hoo: 3, 2,
YunB: L, R, Seong Beom: 2, 1)
(Jin Ho: 3, 4, Hye Seon: 2, 2,
Sung Joo: 0, Seung Yong: 3, 1)
Seong Beom, 1 space forward
and 1 space left.
Jin Ho, 3 spaces forward
and 1 space right.
(Jin Ho moves up to 3rd place.)
Hye Seon, two spaces forward.
It would be a problem
if I were around fifth place,
but I was in first place.
If three manage to get
the right prediction...
and four fail to get the right prediction,
that puts me in a stable spot
to secure a place in the final.
Seung Yong, 1 space forward
and 2 spaces left.
Ji Hoo, 2 spaces forward and 1 space left.
(Round 19 Movement Results)
All players have completed their moves.
(Hye Seon: 3, YunB: 3, Ji Hoo: 2,
Jin Ho: 1,)
(Seung Yong: unknown, Seong Beom: 6,
Keun Woo: 7, Sung Joo: unknown)
Round 20 will begin now.
The movement cards
for each area are revealed.
(The final reveal of the movement cards
that will determine the game)
(Seong Beom)
The moment I failed to get Area C
during Round 19,
I realized this.
We are in desperate need
of Keun Woo's help.
I don't know what Keun Woo is thinking,
but we must work with him in Round 20.
Keun Woo!
Where did you go?
I asked him at that moment,
and he said, "I placed this here."
And fortunately,
that was the area we wanted.
- Keun Woo,
- Yes?
place your card
in the area of your choice.
(Keun Woo's remaining cards)
(Keun Woo bets a 5 on Area B.)
Keun Woo,
you've placed Card Five in Area B.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
Okay. If I get reverse and 2 cards of 2,
I will secure 7th place 100 percent.
When I place the reverse card
on Sung Joo...
and move his car back,
I will secure seventh place.
Seong Beom will secure sixth place.
My car can be abandoned.
I have no chance of taking the win.
Focus on securing your position...
and think about the ways
Hye Seon can lose her lead.
At the final round,
I was pretty much dead.
I gave up on my car.
As for Hye Seon,
it was okay for one other person
to get the right prediction.
As long as there weren't over two,
she had a great chance
of advancing to the final.
Seong Beom was the one in trouble.
This side.
- I can't get that. This is what I need.
- Right.
(Seong Beom must move only 1 space
to secure 6th place.)
Jin Ho, place your card
in the area of your choice.
I had a great time.
(Jin Ho's remaining cards)
I will dream big for the last round.
(Jin Ho bets a 1 on Area A.)
Jin Ho, you've placed Card One in Area A.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
Hye Seon,
you've placed Card One in Area B.
Seong Beom, place your card
in the area of your choice.
Please help me.
Seong Beom,
you've placed Card Four in Area D.
I made my bet for the final round...
and I had this sense of trust.
We only had 4, 1, and 1,
but I felt like
things were going to favor us.
I had a sense of trust...
that we were going to be able to
finish the game off nicely.
All players have placed their bets.
I will announce the betting results.
This result will become history.
Area A...
goes to YunB.
Area B goes to Keun Woo.
Gosh, this is intense.
Area C...
goes to Seung Yong.
(Area C goes to Seung Yong.)
Area D...
has no winners.
What do we do now?
(Sighing)
The winners were announced...
and none from our team were called out.
"Our final blow."
"Let's leave 4 4s..."
"and take all four."
Ji Hoo, you've placed Card Four in Area D.
Seung Yong,
will you place Card Four in Area C?
Yes.
(The Seung Yong Alliance marked all areas
with 4.)
Seong Beom's biggest mistake...
was that he used all of his big cards
before the final round.
It was the best chance
to make their attack,
but they were destroyed by us in the bet.
(The P3 Alliance failed to use
their early turn to their advantage.)
You will now place your movement cards.
(Round 20 Betting Results)
Seung Yong, please place your cards.
What do I do? Gosh, what do I do?
(Seung Yong unexpectedly
gets to place his cards first.)
If Seung Yong moves me forward,
it goes against my predicted rank.
I felt really nervous.
We had the upper hand...
and Seung Yong was the key player.
You have to give me a zero card.
Zero must be given to Ji Hoo.
The other cards must be used.
Keun Woo can reverse with zero.
(The last card of 4
gets placed on Keun Woo's gear board.)
It's over for me.
Did they finish you off? It's over.
The moment four was placed...
my elimination was secured.
How should I use these cards?
Keun Woo, please place your cards.
We have the worst cards.
Even if Keun Woo were to send
Seung Yong forward...
and create a gap,
YunB's team can give Seong Beom 3 and 3.
That will make Seong Beom's car
be next to mine,
but on the inside line.
According to the rules,
the car on the inside line...
is ranked higher
and that makes Seong Beom fifth.
We thought of the best possible move
with those three cards.
"How can we hinder Sung Joo?"
"How can we hinder Seung Yong?"
"How can we protect Hye Seon?"
"How can we make my car move?"
- That seems like the best move.
- Right.
- Let's go with that.
- That seems like the best move.
(The fate of Team P3 Alliance
will be decided by Keun Woo's 3 cards.)
- Seung Yong.
(He places 2 and 2 on Seung Yong's board
and the reverse card on Sung Joo's board.)
Keun Woo moved Seung Yong
two spaces forward.
(Shin Seung Yong: Predicted 6th)
So...
(Seung Yong fails with his prediction.)
he ended up getting eliminated.
- There are no moves left.
- Gosh.
We just fell short.
- I'm one space short.
- Right.
It's okay. Well done.
YunB, please place your cards.
(YunB has the last three cards.)
I didn't expect them to be
this important...
until the very last moment.
YunB had three cards in his hands.
If he moves me forward,
I will get eliminated.
The game has ended.
The race ranks will be announced.
First place,
Choi Hye Seon.
(First place:
Choi Hye Seon, Predicted 3rd)
I was in first place.
If four players fail to make
the right prediction,
I secure a place in the final.
Second place,
Kang Ji Hoo.
Third place, YunB.
For the final round,
our calculations were perfect.
Ji Hoo, two spaces left.
(Ji Hoo's car goes on top of YunB's car
and they each place 2nd and 3rd.)
"YunB and I will survive
if things end like this."
Fourth place, Shin Seung Yong.
(4th place:
Shin Seung Yong, Predicted 6th)
Fifth place, Hong Jin Ho.
(5th place: Hong Jin Ho, Predicted 1st)
Is there a place for the cards?
(The Seung Yong Alliance
didn't know Seong Beom's predicted rank.)
There was nothing I could do
in the final round.
(YunB ended up discarding
all three cards.)
He discarded all three of his cards.
(Seong Beom kept his predicted rank
after a tough game.)
"I did it."
If they figured it out...
and went against him,
Seong Beom would've placed fifth.
Fortunately, they didn't figure it out
until the end.
It was a big relief
to be able to keep Seong Beom.
It was the same with Hye Seon.
Sixth place, Heo Seong Beom.
Seventh place, Hyun Sung Joo.
Eighth place, Jeong Keun Woo.
You overrated yourself.
Soon, the prediction result
will be checked...
to announce the final result.
Gosh.
I will announce the semi-final results.
The players who will advance
to the finals...
after winning the semi-finals are...
Kang Ji Hoo,
YunB,
Heo Seong Beom,
and Hyun Sung Joo.
(Hyun Sung Joo)
Gosh.
- Nice one.
- Gosh.
Sung Joo, choose your predicted rank.
(Hyun Sung Joo: Predicted 7th)
Members of an alliance...
can pull or push each other.
I thought that each team would put
at least one person in the leading group.
Instead of going for 1st, 2nd, or 3rd,
I thought that 4th, 5th, 6th, or 7th...
was a better way to fish
in troubled waters.
I had to be a joker in the pack today.
That was why I went with seventh place
at the end of the race.
(Sung Joo's turn to place
the movement cards early in the race)
Even though my predicted rank was seventh,
I thought that it was important...
to make myself feel like
my predicted rank...
was in the leading group or the middle.
I kept showing the others that I wanted to
to move forward with my cards.
(Impressed)
Are you finally moving?
I wanted to show my eagerness
of wanting to move forward.
I discarded the cards
to show the others...
that I wanted to move forward on my own.
Keun Woo and I were the only ones
with no other teammates.
The one who kept quiet...
suddenly started talking to
Seong Beom and Jin Ho.
It felt like he predicted 6th or 7th.
I knew that it was a competition
between us.
The one who played the game on his own...
started to work with another team.
Instead of solving things on my own
with my cards,
I also started to look for help
due to anxiety.
Did you decide where to place your bet?
(He strategically approached YunB...)
(and Seung Yong.)
To place 7th and 6th,
we needed someone to be in 8th place.
To put Keun Woo in 8th place,
we decided to place
the reverse card on his gear board.
Then, I'll use this on Keun Woo.
(They placed the reverse card and 4
on Keun Woo's gear board.)
After placing the reverse card,
Seung Yong placed four.
That moved Keun Woo further back.
Keun Woo, four spaces backward.
Gosh, I'm last.
(Keun Woo ended up placing 8th.)
"Gosh, this worked. This actually worked."
(Prediction Race Results)
(Ji Hoo: Predicted 2nd, 2nd Place,
YunB: Predicted 3rd, 3rd place)
(Seong Beom: Predicted 6th, 6th place,
Sung Joo: Predicted 7th, 7th place)
(Hye Seon, Seung Yong, Jin Ho, Keun Woo
failed with their predictions.)
Choi Hye Seon,
Shin Seung Yong,
Hong Jin Ho,
and Jeong Keun Woo...
have been eliminated from Bloody Game X.
Please leave the main hall immediately.
- I'll get going! Good luck!
- Good luck!
Good luck, Seong Beom!
I am totally satisfied.
Jeong Keun Woo was able to
reach the semi-finals...
and make a beautiful departure.
I'm very grateful for that.
Hong Jin Ho, Xitsuh, and Lee Tae Gyun.
The plays we made as a four...
will become memories I will never forget.
I was invited again
after being in Season One.
Thank you so much...
for giving me the chance to redeem myself.
And as for myself,
I was able to reach...
the semi-finals.
Thank you so much
for making me feel confident...
about being able to reach
even further in the future.
- Become the champion.
- "Seventh place?"
Great job today.
Things didn't work out.
Getting eliminated
was quite disappointing.
I played many different games
before reaching the semi-finals.
I did my best to stay focused
for each game.
I can confidently say...
that I gave it my all for those games.
After going through three Deathmatches,
I learned about what type of person I was.
It was a great time to learn about myself.
Through Bloody Game,
I've learned a lot of things.
I've achieved my goal...
of wanting to reach the semi-finals,
so I feel happy about that.
I think I'll feel very proud
if Ji Hoo becomes the champion.
- Good luck!
- Good luck, Seong Beom!
- Gosh.
It's disappointing,
but I don't feel any regret.
During the previous season,
I think I was very intimidated.
I lacked confidence and was intimidated.
For this season,
I had a lot more life experience.
I was a lot more active...
and showed a lot more development
than before.
I also enjoyed it a lot more.
Gosh, this is so sad!
I don't want to go home!
I'm able to go home
after an incredible experience.
Thank you so much.
We'll go home together.
- We've survived for a long time.
- Right.
Bloody Game X felt a lot more exciting.
There were many plays that I made...
for a team battle.
I felt a sense of comradeship
very quickly.
I've definitely felt the charms
of a team battle...
through my time here.
After going through
the Bloody Game series,
I've become a lot stronger.
It was tough every time...
and I hated being in the wild.
There were things that could
only be experienced in Bloody Game...
and there were things
I couldn't feel anywhere else.
I loved those moments.
Not being able to reach the final
is quite disappointing,
but as someone who has experienced
Bloody Games 2, 3, and X,
I've truly had a blast.
As I must think positively,
I'm glad that...
Seong Beom has advanced
as our representative.
I'm sure Seong Beom will go
and destroy them all.
- Great job.
- Gosh!
Gosh!
- Become the champion.
- Wasn't that the plan?
- Great work.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
You've made it this far.
- Let's go!
- Thank you.
Ji Hoo! Good luck, Ji Hoo.
- Good luck!
- Thank you.
- Smack their faces...
with your talent.
Good luck!
Seong Beom, give me a call
if the others harass you.
Thank you!
You'll still represent us.
It's the 1-on-1 match you love. Go for it.
- Bye!
- Finish them off!
- I'll get going now.
- Good luck!
- Bye!
(Bloody Game X eliminated players)
(Hong Jin Ho, Jeong Keun Woo,
Shin Seung Yong, Choi Hye Seon)
We've made it this far.
- Great work, everyone!
- Great work, everyone.
- Bye!
Will you be able to handle it?
Team C is full of jerks.
That's betraying Team C.
One must die.
Those wimps.
I will be cheap and dirty.
Gosh!
I did it.
Sang Min!
- Don't do that!
- Gosh, that hurts.
Quiet!
You did well. Don't blank out.
I hope I won't have to cry.
I want to kill them all.
I'm a petty criminal.
We should cut Seung Yong's throat.
What story are you on about?
It was coming.
I don't want any more piggyback rides.
Stop with that!
One space forward.
Reaching the final?
It feels quite all right.
Two of the unorthodox sect
from Bloody Game Two...
and two of the orthodox sect.
Flipping the tables
against everyone's expectations.
That is my strength.
I will take the bull by the horns.
I do believe I'm the underdog,
but I have a good chance of winning.
The ones who were known to be prodigies...
can get their pride hurt
by losing to someone like YunB or me.
We can compete with 120 percent
of what we have,
but they will feel this pressure.
As we have nothing to lose,
I think we will feel very comfortable
in the game.
I will do my best to become the champion.
I thought that I would reach the final
with my talent.
But many of the things I lacked...
were filled by the older ones.
I was able to reach the final
because of their sacrifice.
I will fight until the end
and become the champion.
It was the moment I've always dreamed of.
I've made it this far
with the sacrifice of the others.
I will put my life and beliefs
on the line...
and do my best in the final.
(Kang Ji Hoo)
(Hyun Sung Joo)
(Heo Seong Beom)
(YunB)
(Who will become the final winner
of Bloody Game X?)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)